We can finally intervene.
Kaiju appearing in a world
weakens the barrier.
It's early for two at once.
Go on, Knight! Do your best!
Of course. That's my duty.
What the—?!
A giant?!
What's Our Reason for Coming Together?
— Episode 7 —
Hey, hey, hey! What the hell?!
Get lost!
So fast!
What is that thing?
Is that a kaiju, too?
I can't control it.
Dammit!
—Gridknight Storm!
—Stay still!
Onija, let me take over!
Chill! Just relax!
You guys, let's withdraw for now.
We've got this!
We can beat Gauma this time!
But...
It would be a waste to lose this kaiju.
Fine.
That was close.
It saved us?
Thank god it's not an enemy.
I take it back!
You asked for it!
What?! Where'd it go?!
This ain't over yet!
Dammit! Now it's all beat up!
And to think they entrusted
Dynazenon to me!
Huh?
Hey, Koyomi! Where are you going?!
Eh? What's up with him?
Whatever. Let's look for the kaiju.
Huh?
You guys search from above.
It couldn't have gotten far.
Shit. I've gotta fix it somehow.
We can't fight like this.
I'm not seeing the kaiju.
Sorry. I wasn't watching my energy.
It's no big deal.
Let's just keep an eye on things.
What's with this purple guy?
It's time to change capitals if Tokyo's like this.
Another rampaging kaiju
Shit. Was that giant a kaiju?
Not sure, but I couldn't control it.
We made another enemy.
It's natural to make enemies
when you change things.
Our kaiju was pretty strong.
If we play it right, we can win.
You're surprisingly pumped up.
Something happen?
No.
Ah! You're pissed
'cuz that guy hugged you!
Hey, hey! Looks like Mujina's
got a cute side—
It's not like that.
I messed things up.
I'm just taking responsibility for it.
I knew it.
This is Arata. Uh, my husband.
She always talks about you, Yamamoto.
You've known her since middle school,
right? Was she always like this?
You work nearby?
Hmm? You could say that.
I... help people in need.
That's amazing!
Are you okay, uh, Tachibana?!
Hello?! Anyone there?!
Found you.
Gauma sure is late.
Are you mad?
I'm not mad.
Yeah, you are.
He's back.
I feel like shit right now.
The kaiju?
No use. Couldn't find it.
I see.
I'm starving. Let's grab something to eat.
Sorry about earlier... For teasing you.
But you being serious
for a change ain't half bad.
Just so we're clear,
we don't fight to settle
personal grudges, you know?
The power of kaiju
isn't for killing people.
It's for killing humanity as a whole.
I don't always get
the things you guys say,
but I'll go along with it this time.
Thanks for the meal!
Man, I'm stuffed!
That's better! Now we're pumped
and ready to roll, right?
What? Sure.
Thanks for the meal.
Jeez, there you are! I finally found you!
Chise?
Why are you here?
What a mean thing to say
to a comrade in arms!
I know, but...
Hmm? Where's Senpai?
Who the hell knows? He ran off.
Huh? On his own?
Yeah, and hope he comes back quick.
We'll be up all night.
Huh? All night?
Waiting for the kaiju.
What about you guys?
I'll stay, too.
Huh?
I'll tell my parents I'm staying
at a friend's house.
Me, too.
That's more like it.
They're working well together.
Yeah. Not bad.
You were saved by this purple guy?
Is he a friend?
Nah, he picked a fight right after.
What's his deal?
Yeah?
—Minam—
—Hey!
Koyomi! Where have you been?!
Senpai, don't worry me like that!
Sorry.
Huh? That's all? Did something happen?
That was you guys?
That was your atrocious fighting?
Atrocious?
Knight, please don't be
so rude right off the bat.
Who the hell are you?
We're the Gridknight Alliance.
Uh, the name's not important though.
What the hell?
We protect the world
from the threat of kaiju!
Protect the world... from kaiju?
How's that purple guy involved?
That would be me.
Huh? You mean, you become that?
You transform?
Whoa. Talk about fantasy.
I thought that red guy was
a kaiju, but I guess not.
Your ragtag crew got wrecked.
You mean, Dynazenon?
Dynazenon. That's its name?
So? Did you come to fight kaiju?
That's right! Which is why
we want to cooperate with you.
Cooperate?
Yup! And speaking of which...
We can use this Fixer—
No thanks!
Huh?
These guys are shady as hell.
They roll up on us out of nowhere?
You're one to talk.
I see.
I'd rather not work with the wounded.
You'll only hold me back.
Say what?
I'm stating the truth.
Which is it? You wanna cooperate with us,
or are you picking a fight?
I see what you're saying.
Let's go, Knight... For now.
Right.
What's up with them?
Get on the same page first.
Was that smart, Gauma? Dynazenon's broken,
so shouldn't we fight together?
Dynazenon. When kaiju appear
in a world, so does opposition—
like antibodies that rise to defend it.
Yeah. But it seems pretty obvious
that they're not bad people.
I just want to make sure of it.
It doesn't heal with time after all.
Gauma.
Mmm?
Earlier, I went to save someone...
A person I think I hate.
I see. Good on you.
Somebody once told me something:
"It's best to live honestly
with your feelings."
Was it the same person
you're searching for?
Yeah.
What kind of person was she?
Someone who lived
in a world I couldn't reach.
And...
And?
A total beauty.
She's the one who entrusted
Dynazenon to you?
Cool, right?
Sure is.
Authorized Personnel Only
DO NOT ENTER
JAPAN EXPRESSWAY
I wonder what Gauma plans to do.
We can't exactly fight kaiju like this.
You always carry that, huh?
Are you hot? Maybe I'll go buy something.
This... It was Kano's.
I always wanted to play with it.
Kano! Can I try it, too?
You're never getting it.
When Kano...
When my sister and I were little,
we got along just fine.
But before long, we grew apart.
Even at home, I hardly saw her smile.
So when I saw her in that video
smiling and having fun in chorus club,
it kinda surprised me.
But the one time she invited me
to her recital, she was smiling.
I don't know why, but...
I thought, maybe she wanted to
get along again like we had in the past.
But that was the last time I saw her.
If Kano was really bullied...
If she really committed suicide...
I wonder why she smiled at me that day?
I honestly have no idea.
I guess I know nothing about Kano.
Hmm?
Uh, sorry.
Why are you crying?
I don't know. I really don't know.
But you still don't know
if it was suicide or not.
You still don't know why she was smiling.
Let's keep investigating more.
But she was just a stranger to you.
She was your sister.
If she was a part of you,
she's not some stranger.
What?
Your face.
S-Sorry.
Talk about a runny nose.
I know. It's a snotty mess.
Yomogi.
Yeah?
Thanks.
I'll get us some ice cream.
Wait. I'll come, too.
You okay, Mujina? Need a break?
I'm fine. I don't get tired
when connected to kaiju.
Real kaiju users don't sleep.
Hey, get up.
It's the kaiju. Dynazenon's not
in good shape, but we've got no choice.
Dynazenon!
Battle—!
Dynazenon! This time,
we're gonna whoop your ragtag ass!
Your ragtag crew got wrecked.
So what?! Being ragtag
is what brought us together!
Still not sure about them?
No. Let's do it.
We don't need help.
Don't get me wrong. It wasn't to help you.
Knight Bursting Light Bomb!
Something Beam!
The kaiju's stronger than before.
Knight, I'll use Fixer Beam!
You sure? We only have one.
That's why I'm using it now!
Dynazenon! It's time to
get your power back!
Dynazenon healed!
Huh? How?
Now we can fight to our heart's content!
There's two of them and two of us!
There's no excuse to lose!
Right! We won't be beat!
Gridknight Circular!
Dyna Saber!
—Big Blade Strike!
—Knight Circular End!
If not for the irregular, we had that.
Irregulars come because of kaiju.
It's a good omen.
Next time... Next time,
we'll do even better.
You know it.
You saved our asses! Uh...
This is Knight. Gridknight.
And me, I'm the Second.
The Second?
Of what?
I've gotta say thanks
for healing Dynazenon—!
Keep your hands to yourself.
Sorry.
Until next time, guys!
Shoot! It's this late?!
Going somewhere?
To school!
Let's hurry. We might make it.
Access Mode... Dyna Wing!
"For Kisarazu Station"
He said that you saved him! Thank you!
It helped us realize we should
value each other more.
Mmm.
Thanks so much! Until now, I didn't—
Will you come along if I
look into Kano some more?
Yeah. What's the plan?
I need to find this person—Futaba Senda.