Gauma...
Yomogi, may I?
He's healing?
No. It's not a Fixer Beam,
but it should ease his pain.
We won't get an ambulance like this.
Hang in there, Gauma. Knight.
It's a kaiju!
What's going on?
I thought no more would appear.
The world of kaiju isn't over just yet!
What's up, Juuga?
This kaiju...!
Could it be?!
It's Sizumu?!
Take me with you, Sizumu!
I wanna see a future with kaiju!
How about you two?
I choose a future where more humans die.
In the end, this is all I can do.
What the—?!
This guy powered up even more?!
Gauma!
Thank goodness!
You okay?!
Am I okay?
Your face tells me
all I need to know.
I don't think... I've got long.
Stop it.
What are you saying?
Yomogi... Yume...
Sorry for getting you involved
in this kaiju user mess.
All that happened 5,000 years ago
has nothing to do with you guys.
It has nothing to do with us?!
Gauma, you brought us
into it yourself! With Dynazenon!
You're the reason
we all built this connection!
I'm sorry.
No, that's not it...
Thanks.
Tell Koyomi for me.
Tell him yourself.
Live and tell him in your own words!
Not so loud.
Kaiser Knight Double Storm!
Let's go, Yomogi. There's still
something we can do.
Second, take care of Gauma.
Yeah. Be careful.
See you later.
Mmm.
The train has come to an emergency stop. We apologize—
It's all a coincidence, just like that day.
But what's different... is me.
What are you doing?!
If I don't beat that kaiju,
those guys will lose their future.
I sure as hell didn't revive for a long, easy life.
But you're in no shape for it!
In this world, there's three...
important things... you've gotta keep.
Promises, love, and...
I like you.
Will you go out with me?
In the end, she never answered.
I missed my chance.
Don't touch me!
Mujina?!
Ouch...
It's okay, Kano. I'm fine.
Yomogi?!
Let's go, Minami!
Everyone's waiting for us!
Mmm!
Goldburn! Tell me you're alive!
You really are the coolest friend
I've got in the world!
No killing Chise's friend!
I'm sick of memorials!
Knight!
Yomogi Asanaka?
Gauma?!
I came to give Koyomi my apologies.
Sorry to get you involved.
Gauma...
What are we talking about?
I see. Guess I never told you.
Gauma, I said to wait. Why are you here?
I'm here to help
whether you like it or not.
Then don't regret it.
It's time to combine our powers!
Right!
Super Dragon King Kaiser Gridknight!
Slaughter all humans!
Kaiju are gonna wipe you all out!
Yeah
Just put your trust in me it's gonna work out alright
We're not gonna let that happen!
Yeah! That's right!
I can convince you even if it's gonna take all night
Kaiser Knight Circular!
Cause there's something in my mind
Gauma!
I can picture inside me
It took away my breath
And my heart is breathing faster
It's chemistry at work
whenever we're together
I looked up to you! I needed you,
and you needed me!
A sign
Something tells me that you're gonna fall
For my charms and my affection
And yet, you betrayed us!
Move in my direction
And yet, I only liked you more!
Let me show I'm never wrong
Shuddap!
I can tell this situation
I said not to show your face!
The one that we've been waiting
All this time, I know!
This time, I'm gonna
make sure you stay dead!
Yes I know!
All I have is kaiju!
There is no pressure, you can take it at your own time
I realized they're all I've got,
and Koyomi's to blame!
Just think it over cause my confidence is justified
If it's my fault, then I'm sorry!
I can tell the way you look, you're right to be suspicious
Even if you apologize,
I'll never forgive you!
My tension overrides all your superstitions
I'll break the spell that's binding you
I can tell you I've seen the signs
Get off me!
Something tells me that you're gonna fall
For my charms and my affection
Move in my direction
Sizumu!
Let me show I'm never wrong
He's not gonna talk to us, is he?
I can tell this situation
The one that we've been waiting
All this time, I see the signs
Rex...
For my charms and my affection
...Grid...
Move in my direction
...Fire!
Let me show I'm never wrong
I can tell this situation's
The one that we've been waiting
All this time, I know!
Hang on, guys!
Don't you lose to this!
Yomogi! What are you doing?!
Back then, it might've
been a coincidence, but...!
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
Instance Domination!
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realize your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Now!
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
Combine Dragon Dynazenon!
When I met you, you were all alone
I want to know why you were looking so lorn
Battle...
...Go!
Stand proud!
And followed by Dynazenon Full Burst!
It all depends on us!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
Come, Goldburn!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
What?!
When protecting the one they care about
Anyone can become the hero of their own little story, for sure!
Dynazenon
Super Dragon Dyna Rex!
Drop dead, you phoney kaiju!
Something had been missing, I was left discontent
Let's end this, Gridknight!
The days kept tearing holes in my heart
Right! Together!
Blazing Hot Inferno...
But you were the missing piece, you completed me
...Burning...
...Grid...
...Rex...
And right now I'll proudly put on display all I've learned
...Roar!
Stand proud!
It's not over yet!
It all depends on us!
No! This is the end for you!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I never thought I'd die again.
I'll take it hand in hand
Is it better this way?
Alright it's go time
No. Kaiju will have their future yet.
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Gauma?!
Huh?
Gauma!
Yomogi, let's get him to the hospital!
Right!
Nah... I don't wanna be
any more of a bother.
Huh?
In this world, I couldn't meet you, but...
...I got to meet them.
I think I finally know the reason why...
...you entrusted Dynazenon to me.
Huh? What about Gauma?
That scared me.
He's saying, "Let's not drag this out."
Your friend looks better now.
Yeah. He's all healed up.
Who are you again?
Huh? Remember me already.
Gauma said in this world,
it's important to keep
three things, right?
three things.
Promises, love, and...
Um...
We must leave this world
for our next mission.
Thanks for everything, guys.
Same here. Thank you, Knight... Second.
Thank you, Dynazenon.
Thank you, Goldburn!
You're the best friend I've ever had!
Thank you!
They're gone.
Yeah.
We should get going.
Ugh.
Don't "ugh" me.
What's up?
Nothing.
I so don't wanna go.
Still saying that?
Well...
Didn't we promise to make it a success?
Respect for the Aged Day
Recital
Well, if you insist...
Entry Prohibited
Ayanashi City
Ayame Public Middle School
Senpai, how many interviews did you botch?
Twenty-one.
In the end, it was your ex's husband
who got you a job?
She's not my ex.
She's a friend.
You schmoozed your way in?
Of course I did.
Now I really don't wanna end up like you.
It's best if you don't.
You look so weird in a suit.
And you looked weird in a uniform.
I could never pull one off.
Fujiyokidai High School
"My Good Friends"
ENO.24   Mei Kakui
Hey, I said not to use me.
Did you?
I did.
Yume, should you be here?
Isn't it your turn?
Shut up, Mom.
You haven't changed.
Isn't your turn coming up soon?
Yeah. You can pay at the entrance.
Okay.
Hey, is Gauma coming?
Nope.
He got banned from our school.
Huh? Why? What did he do?
Yomo!
Yomogi!
What's up?
Minami's not coming.
What's her deal? If you won't help prep,
at least help the day of!
Huh?
She's coming up next,
but we can't reach her.
Yomogi, go find her.
You're on Minami duty!
R-Right!
Hello, everyone!
We're the calligraphy club!
The recent kaiju have caused terrible
damage to Fujiyokidai and the area.
In your heart, you are...
The calligraphy club extends our
deepest sympathies to all the victims.
A white, white bird
with huge wings...
We hope our performance puts smiles
on everyone's faces, so please enjoy!
There you are!
It's our turn to run the cafe,
so let's head back.
I really don't want to.
I know, but just do it
for the others in our class.
It's time to go.
Then take me with you.
I just don't get it.
You had the potential to be
a kaiju user, but you wasted it.
I don't understand kaiju,
so I could never do it.
Kaiju can't be understood by people.
They're beyond logic and reason.
They're not bound by anything.
You witnessed it, right?
The power of kaiju
Minami
Family Grave
can free one from
time, space, and even death.
You could've grasped the greatest of freedoms.
Won't you regret it?
I don't know yet.
But I wanna live through all the good
and bad things that happen in my life.
You people lose your freedom,
unaware of it happening,
and eventually, lose yourself.
I'm not losing my freedom.
It's more like I'm gaining
irreplaceable bonds.
I just don't get it.
Yomogi?
Well done.
You're quite the joker, Minami.
Hey...
You're still saying "Minami."
Everyone's waiting... C'mon, Yume!
Well done!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Embarrassment can be a good thing.
Our scars aren't healing.
I hope they stay with us forever.
Why?
So we remember,
no matter how many years pass.
What Was I Entrusted With?
— Final Episode —