Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realize your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
When I met you, you were all alone
I want to know why you were looking so lorn
Stand proud!
It all depends on us!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Dynazenon... What exactly are you?
Before we're beat,
show us what you're made of!
D... y... n... a... R... e... x...?
Huh?
Stand proud!
It all depends on us! We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness and all your weakness
Th-That stopped it!
Is this Dynazenon's true power?! Dyna Rex!
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Blazing Inferno Rex Roar!
What... just happened?
Minami, you okay?!
What's this?
It vanished!
It can go back to being small?
It's thanks to you guys
we beat that kaiju. Thanks.
Huh? But I didn't do anything.
Actually, it's possible that Dynazenon
recognized your aptitude.
Thank goodness!
You're not dead after all, Senpai!
Oh, Chise.
Where'd the big robot go?
I guess it shrunk.
Where's your umbrella, Minami?
Huh? Shrunk?
What?
Hell no.
Huh?
You! Apologize to Yomogi!
What the hell?! You were about to leave!
Apologize for breaking
your promise with Yomogi!
Acheron Flood Gate
Lorem Ip
sum Dolor
Sit Amet
Wednesday, May 27
Just forget it!
Why?!
'Cuz it hardly matters right now.
What are we talking about?
Huh? Who are you?
Koyomi Yamanaka.
I'm Chise Asukagawa. We're cousins.
I'm Gauma. And you? What's your name?
Yume Minami.
Just chill out, okay?
Anyway, what's this about
kaiju and Dynazenon?
That kaiju was being controlled.
Probably by the Kaiju Eugenicists,
a dangerous crew.
Kaiju Eugenicists?
How do you know?
They're kaiju users like me,
and I know they'll be back.
There's gonna be more kaiju?
To get ready for when they come,
you guys need Dynazenon training.
Let's meet up here tomorrow.
Huh? Tomorrow, I dunno...
You guys are fine with it?
If everyone else comes, sure.
Especially you. Promise me
that you'll show up.
Fine.
Dynazenon... Are you a kaiju?
Why did that person trust you with me?
I'm this way.
Right.
Yomogi! You're being tricked!
She's toying with you and tricked you!
What's Your Reason for Fighting?
— Episode 2 —
Whoa! That's sick!
Which one's the kaiju?
Both of 'em?
Hey, listen up!
Uh, transportation is a huge mess
because of yesterday's kaiju incident.
Classes will start with 3rd period today.
Huh?!
Sensei! Tell us before we leave home!
It just got decided!
And periods will be shorter, so—
Why is our school so slow with announcements?
My friend's school—
Senpai. Training is this evening,
right? Care if I come?
Sure, why not?
Must be nice to get your own robot!
You'll get paid for this, right?
Huh? We get money?
What if you did?
Uh, then that means... I'm employed.
Work again, Yomogi?
Yeah. You doing something?
Meat skewers. Kaneishi wants some.
He's got work.
What a busy bee.
Sorry. See ya.
Yeah, later.
Bye-bye.
Yomogi's working so much these days.
Does he need money that badly?
He wants to be independent.
Dogs must be leashed
Lorem
Ipsum
A
B
C
Dogs must be leashed
Wait! Wait!
Put me down!
Gotta go.
That's rare. You got plans?
Oh, wait.
Hmm?
What the heck?
Later!
Good grief, that girl...
Maybe I should've gone to training.
How was your date yesterday?
Believe me, it was anything but that.
Something happen?
Way too much happened.
Erotically?
Not erotically.
Oh. She's here.
Oh? You came after all! Atta girl!
Where's Yomogi?!
Huh? He's not coming?!
What are we doing?
I told you already! Pilot training!
Stand out much?
Should we go to the mountains for this?
Right now?
We can just go in your toys.
It's possible Dynazenon
recognized your aptitude.
Oh.
You were in here? Sorry.
Gauma? Why are you here?!
Because you weren't at—
Close the door!
Oh, sorry.
Why'd you come in?
Yomogi. Why didn't you come to training?
You came to my house just to ask me that?
I told you, I had work.
Is it that important?
I'm finally old enough to work, so...
I see.
Aren't you cramped?
I am.
I told you, it's too small.
Oh? So now it's my fault?
I never—
She's toying with you and tricked you!
Is it true?
I said I was sorry.
It didn't sound like you were sorry.
Maybe I should just apologize.
What a good bath!
Mmm.
Why did you let a stranger inside?
He said he was your friend.
And you just believed him?
Be a little cautious!
I know! Why don't you eat with us?
You're not listening.
Well, I'd hate to intrude
more than I have.
As you can see,
Imose City Hall is a disaster.
Why don't you go sleep, Mom?
It's a six-floor building,
but roughly four floors were torn apart.
Mmm.
This is incredibly good!
Thank you.
I really appreciate the feast!
There are what appears to be claw marks
from a kaiju on the building.
I know! It's late,
so why don't you sleep over?
To protect city hall,
this tent will be used as disaster HQ.
Huh?! Why?!
Well, I'd hate to intrude more than—
Due to the incident,
this train service has been suspended.
We're very sorry for any—
So it's impossible for Achilles
to catch up to the tortoise.
If Achilles gets here,
he hasn't caught up, yes?
He's here, see? Not caught up.
This paradox is—
You didn't come yesterday.
To training? Yeah, I had work.
I want you to come with me somewhere.
I guess here works.
I practiced enough to use this now.
Oh, that Dynazenon thing?
Access Mode... Dyna Wing!
What?! You're kidding!
You, too.
Me?!
Access Mode...
...Dyna Soldier.
Huh?
Gauma said we should practice this, too.
Whoa! We're floating!
I'm sorry about breaking that promise.
Why did you do that?
Forget it.
Are you mad?
No. I'm over it.
Sorry.
So, this becomes Dynazenon
if everyone combines?
I think so.
In that case, what's the name
of what we are now?
Its name? No clue.
Dyna... uh, Wing Soldier?
Where to now?
Um, is it this way?
Is this where we fought the other day?
Yeah.
It was dark and I couldn't tell,
but we sure made a mess.
Yeah.
Why come here?
I wanted to see it in person.
It's only like this
because we fought, right?
But if we hadn't fought,
I think it would've been worse.
Think we'll have to keep on fighting?
Shouldn't we just
hand this off to somebody?
Somebody?
Like, the nation.
The government or something.
If you always go by the book,
there're things you can't protect.
Yet we go home by train.
When I was in elementary school,
my big sister died.
Huh?
By accident.
She died at that flood gate.
Next stop is Fujiyokidai. Fujiyokidai.
Use the doors on the left. Please remain—
We've got training today. You coming?
I've got another shift today.
I see. I'll let the others know.
Thanks. Later.
Whoa! Awesome, Senpai!
He's pretty dang good now,
don't you think?
Sure is.
Great, you came again! What about Yomogi?
He can't make it.
Again?!
Ah, there it is.
Those are some crazy colors.
It came surprisingly quick.
Maybe it chained well.
Who's gonna get this one?
Seems like a good one for Juuga.
I suppose.
What if that thing interferes?
Leave it to me. I'll show no mercy.
Instance Domination.
Kaiju shall steer the world.
B
"[Breaking] Another gigantic kaiju-like creature discovered in Tokyo."
Look!
Abort! Abort training!
What's the matter?
A kaiju appeared! Let's go!
Yume, can you contact Yomogi?
Contact?
If I go through friends, maybe.
I didn't go to training again, but...
Hello?
Yomogi!
Another kaiju appeared!
A kaiju?
Without you, we can't fight as Dynazenon!
But I haven't been training.
Don't worry about it. You can just
ride along, but we need you here!
Where are you?!
Where? Um...
Forget it. I see you.
You do?
I knew it'd show up.
Dynazenon! Battle, Go!
What the hell?! It's too fast!
It's not just fast. It's warping.
Warping?!
I'm just along for the ride, right?
It's no use! I can't
figure out its movements!
Split up and fight!
Split up?
Disperse!
Um...
Got it? Fight as three
till I can get a good shot!
Um...
Got it.
Okay.
But I don't really know how to move yet.
Got it.
Okay.
Good! Commence strategy!
C'mon, Yomogi! Move!
Sorry! I'm not sure how!
Supervisor
Incoming
Remind Me
Supervisor
Incoming
Remind Me
Message
Supervisor
Incoming
Remind Me
Message
Supervisor
Incoming
Remind Me
Message
Shoot! It's a call from work!
Quit slacking off, Yomogi!
I'm not being useless on purpose!
Huh? I caught it!
It's gone.
Shit! And it's all my fault!
Yomogi, it's probably the wings.
Wings?
Before it warps, it spreads its wings.
Huh? What if I hold it so it can't?
Yomogi, let's try
working together this time.
How?
The thing we did before.
Let's do it.
Mmm.
Just put your trust in me it's gonna work out alright
I can't convince you even if it's gonna take all night
Dyna Soldier Wing Combine!
Cause there's something in my mind
I can't picture inside me
It took away my breath
And my heart is beating faster
There's chemistry at work
What's the big idea?!
Whenever we're together
Who cares if you changed form?!
The sign
Something tells me that you're gonna fall
For my charms and my affection
Move in my direction
Let me show I'm never wrong
If I can protect, I will!
I can tell the situation's
The one that we've been waiting
All this time, I see the signs
For my charms and my affection
Gotcha!
Yomogi, hang on!
Move in my direction
Let me show I'm never wrong
I can tell the situation's
What?!
The one that we've been waiting
All this time, I know!
Now!
Toss it, Yomogi!
Dyna Launcher...
...Burst Missile!
Senpai and those guys won again!
We won.
That's right. We won.
That was some pretty
sweet teamwork, you three.
Aren't you glad?
We protected it.
Sorry. I held you guys back.
Maybe.
When I was in elementary school,
my big sister died.
Hey, Minami.
What?
Were you fond of your big sister?
Nah, we didn't get along well.
But I'm not sure anymore.
I never thought we'd meet again, Gauma.
I knew it had to be you guys!
Are those people the...?
Yeah. The Kaiju Eugenicists.
Kaiju users like me!
I wanted to have a chat since you were looking a little downcast
So I tried walking a whole step closer to you than usual
The shadows were growing like a clock's hand as the sun set
The next season was calling me as you hurried down the road
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Just like your smiling face