You were looking a little downcast and I wanted to have a chat
So I tried walking a whole step closer alongside you
The shadows were growing like a sundial's needle at sunset
You were striding so fast I thought the season'd change
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Like your smiling face