Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realise your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
I want to know why I met you solus
I want to know the reason for your solitude
Stand proud!
It all depends on us! We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness and all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed