Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realize your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
I want to know why I met you all on your own
I want to know the reason for your solitude
Stand proud!
It all depends on us!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Is Minami not coming today?
Whoa!
He's such a slacker. Yomogi, get a grip!
Get a grip!
Dude, why can't you focus?
That's what I'd like to know.
Whoa!
Wow.
He fell again.
Are you okay?
Sorry, but it's almost time for work.
What's up?
Gauma, where's Minami?
Ah, she called saying
she had to go meet someone.
...she's stood up a bunch of guys.
Oh, I see. Okay.
See ya.
Such a slacker.
Departing
Please Hold The Handrail
So, Minami's meeting someone, huh?
It'd be weird if I asked about it.
What Is This Thumping Heart?
— Episode 4 —
My impression of Kano?
Is that what this is about?
Pretty much.
Hmm.
She was super serious
with practice and stuff.
But everyone loved her
'cuz she was cheerful.
Cheerful?
Yeah.
I see.
Hmm?
That's different than the Kano I knew.
Really?
Oh, and I think Kano picked out
the song for that recital.
And yet...
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. I wanted to meet you
to learn stuff like that.
Hmm. Sorry I'm not much help.
No, it's okay.
Wait. I think Urita might have a few videos.
Videos?
Yeah. Of chorus practice
for the club records.
I bet Kano's in 'em a bunch.
Want his number?
Is that okay?
Of course. Urita would be happy to help.
Thank you.
Hey. Are you going around
asking people about Kano?
Yeah. I've always been
a little curious, so...
I see. I'll let you know if I
think of something. Good luck.
Hey, you okay? Feeling sick?
Was I that zoned out?
By that look, I'd say you're in love.
Huh?
You've been acting sneaky lately.
You like someone, don't you?
It's not like that.
Maybe I do.
Ooh!
Gimme a break.
But it's a wonderful thing.
Even a granny like me went through
a season or two of love.
I bet.
Who's a granny?!
Didn't you say it yourself?
Freshman, get with it and
make your move before it's too late.
Too late...
Ask her out on a date.
A date?!
You're sick after all.
Inamoto
It's been so long,
let's catch up over dinner someday.
Today
Huh? Wh-What's this?
What does it mean? Is this like... a date?
Hey, quit your mumbling over there.
Y-You were here?
Huh? Have been since morning.
Oh, right. Yeah.
Did you meet the chorus grad?
Yeah.
Alone?
You sure have changed.
I'm a big girl high-schooler now, Mom.
Cut it out.
Who made you change?
It's not from anyone's influence.
Smirk much?
It must be rough working
mornings and nights. Poor guy.
Well, it's easy compared to
5,000 years ago.
I can imagine.
Yomogi, is your cold getting worse?
Shoot, I've gotta go.
Thanks for breakfast.
You can skip training today.
Crap, I'm gonna be late.
How is that fair?
Fujiyokidai High School
Hurry, hurry! Hurry, hurry!
Uh, allow me to introduce
the exchange students
transferring to our school.
No way.
Seriously?
Go figure. He's in our class.
I'm hoping for a wonderful
experience in Japan.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Thank you, Sizumu. For your seat,
just take the one behind Minami.
Moving on, I have a few
announcements to make.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah. Nice to meet you.
That wasn't just some coincidence, right?
What?
Why's your face red?
Uh, it's my cold.
Where is Dynazenon? You guys should know.
Huh?
Not here.
It's hidden far away.
But I just saw it flying.
He saw.
I was gonna be late!
You can't use it like that!
I'm not here to fight.
I ask because I'm curious about you two.
Seeing as how I'm an exchange student,
I hope we can all get along.
That sure caught me off guard.
His outfit?
What?
He said he's not here to fight,
but shouldn't we tell Gauma?
But you know he'd charge right in.
No Trespassing
He might.
Say what?! That's bullshit!
You guys used to get along with Gauma
5,000 years ago, right?
Back then, maybe.
This conversation...
Why?
Maybe you can work it out without kaiju.
They'll appear even if we do.
Do you guys make the kaiju?
No. They grow by people's wills.
The Eugenicists don't create kaiju.
We just want to create a world
where kaiju are needed.
You're not kaiju users, are you?
Hard to say.
I don't think so,
but Gauma believes we are.
What makes you think
you need to fight kaiju?
Deep inside, maybe you just
want to fight them?
That's not it. We're just
doing what we can.
Why are kaiju born?
People may seem free,
but everyone's bound by something.
It's kaiju that frees them
from that something.
Where the hell are you hiding?!
It's Gauma.
What's with his outfit?
Huh?
I'm not hiding.
What are you plotting
by approaching these guys?!
Can't a transfer student make friends?
Friends, my ass!
I'll slug you in the kisser!
He dodged!
You gave it away.
I'll slug you! I'll slug you so hard!
You little...!
You're asking for it, bastard!
What's this about?!
Huh? Uh, I came to see someone.
You're coming with us!
You've got all it wrong! Let go!
Let go of me!
Would you behave?!
Let go! I can explain myself!
The hell was Sizumu thinking?
He can hear kaijus' voices,
so perhaps he has a plan.
Can I add the savory white custard?
Is that all?
It's a cold for sure. Stay home.
No, I can't. Ugh, my head hurts.
Don't be silly! You want to
spread it to everyone?!
Mom, you're so loud!
Were you okay after that?
Yeah.
They reported you?
Yeah, and I got fired from my job.
I got screwed. Next time,
I'll be more careful.
Where's Yomogi?
Oh, he's got a nasty cold.
Probably won't be coming for a while.
Wouldn't it be bad if a kaiju came?
You totally want that.
Oh, Gauma. I need a day off next week.
You have every day off!
Yume, check up on Yomogi after school.
Huh? What's the point if it's just a cold?
Yomogi's been slacking lately
like his heart isn't in it.
How is that my problem?
If you hadn't made him wait in the rain,
he wouldn't be sick.
Acheron Flood Gate
T
#THEFUCK
I found a kaiju.
What a weird one. Strange power.
I haven't zoned out like this in a while.
Freshman, get with it and
make your move before it's too late.
Ask her out on a date.
Date...
Something is wrong with me.
When she's like that,
it ain't easy for me.
Here to visit?! How nice of you to come!
By the tone of her voice,
I bet it's just Gauma.
Hmm? You're sleeping.
And here I bought all this stuff.
You're up.
Huh? What?
That's trippy.
It's a very kaiju-like power.
It's like it shifts dimensions.
Whatever. Go for it, Mujina!
Instance Domination.
Gauma said I should check up on you.
I see.
What are you looking at?
Huh? You have stuff you don't want seen?
Not really. No.
I'm kidding.
I didn't know you told jokes.
Huh? Just what do you take me for?
Well, I guess we only started talking recently.
True.
I heard from Gauma that you couldn't
come to training the other day.
Yeah.
'Cuz you were meeting someone.
Yeah. A chorus club grad.
Chorus club?
Oh, for your sister.
They knew a bit about her,
but it wasn't like they knew her well.
I see.
But they put me in touch
with someone. A guy.
A guy?
Yeah.
You okay?
Yeah. F-Fine.
It's Gauma.
Kaiju?
Yume! Come quick with Dyna Wing!
Got it.
I think... you're in no shape to help.
But—!
Give me yours.
Huh? Dyna Soldier?
Yeah. We gotta do everything we can.
Before it's too late.
Too late...
Thanks. We'll have someone pilot it.
Yeah. Be careful.
Get some rest.
You can eat that.
Access Mode... Dyna Striker!
Access Mode... Dyna Diver!
There they are.
Eat this!
That's not gonna work!
Why'd it go through, dammit?!
Where's Yume?!
Gauma, Yomogi's too sick to fight.
I brought Dyna Soldier instead.
We can't combine without a pilot for it!
It's my time to shine!
Wh-When did you—?!
Chise Asukagawa will pilot Dyna Soldier!
Okay! Go for it!
Hey! Who said it's up to you?!
Access Mode... Dyna Soldier!
I did it! I did it! I really did it!
She did it.
What now?
Let's combine and fight!
Can you, Chise?
Yeah! If I think of it as a game!
Hey! What happened to combining?!
I wish I could, but...!
Crush the little one, Mujina!
Quit bossing me around!
Hey, Chise! Look out!
Chise!
Thanks, Senpai.
Don't make me go to another memorial.
Deep inside, maybe you just
want to fight them?
What makes you think
you need to fight kaiju?
That's what I'd like to know.
How is it, Minami?
Real ugly.
Huh? I should come.
Yeah. We might need you.
Having said that, how do I get there?
It's not like I can borrow Mom's car.
Yomogi, hop in!
We can only buy her so much time!
Chise, let's switch!
I-I'd appreciate it!
Dyna Soldier Wing Combine!
Y-Yomo, are you okay?
I-I'm far from okay!
All right, let's combine!
Right!
Combine Dragon Dynazenon!
Dynazenon...
...Battle, Go!
Something Beam!
Penetrator Gun!
Mujina, focus!
Your shouting doesn't help!
Burst Missile Kick!
Let's finish it!
Achoo!
Right!
Super Dragon Dyna Rex!
Up you go! Heave ho!
Eat this!
Blazing Inferno...
...Rex Roar!
Damn that Gauma!
Good work.
You, too.
Let's go.
I thought I was dead.
Thank you!
You're a lifesaver, Yomo! I'll do my best
to train as your Dyna Soldier backup!
You don't have to.
By next week, I'll...
No! I'll combine by tomorrow!
Dynazenon... Can anyone pilot you?
What makes you so sure?
If you can do it, I can, too!
How rude.
Want a ride?
Huh?
What?
Thanks for coming to get me.
I should've brought you along
from the start.
Can I come along next time?
Next time?
When you go asking about your sister.
Sure, but why?
I want to know more about you, too.
Sorry. What was that?
Nothing.
Stand! Bow!
Good morning.
Uh, don't forget that your second period
will be in the language lab today. Also—
Huh?
I guess I caught it.
You were looking a little downcast and I wanted to have a chat
So I tried walking a whole step closer alongside you
The shadows were growing like a sundial's needle at sunset
You were striding so fast I thought the season'd change
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Just like your smiling face