Are those people the...?
Yeah. The Kaiju Eugenicists.
Kaiju users like me!
They made the Kaiju go on a rampage!
Meaning, they're our enemy!
Gauma, did you forget that we're comrades?
Huh? C-Comrades?
That was way in the past!
Why don't you join us,
just like old times?
I'm not—
Screw that!
What kind of idiot
would take in this traitor?!
Joining you guys is the last thing I'd do!
Since we finally reunited,
I think I'll kill you!
Bring it on, if you think you can!
Your phoney Kaiju seems like
it doesn't want to fight.
Guess not.
Too bad! I'm gonna rip—
Hold up, Onija. Without a Kaiju,
we don't stand a chance.
We don't stand a chance?!
Right.
We'll let him off the hook.
Can we leave after this?
Probably.
So be it! You get to live another day.
But next time, I'll kill you!
He's such an idiot.
Are you Kaiju users, too?
Uh, no, we're not—
That's right! They've got
the aptitude for it!
That's why they can move Dynazenon.
Dynazenon...
See you again soon.
What is a Traitor?
— Episode 3 —
Again, soon?
Whoa! Uh-oh!
You guys have it rough
with morning training.
Will you head to school after this?
Oh... Nah, I don't go.
You don't go to school?
When I grow up, I wanna be like Koyomi.
But I did go to middle school.
Besides, I'm not clever like you guys.
I wouldn't say we're clever.
Why don't you join us?
...this traitor!
Traitor? Referring to Gauma?
Yomogi, stay focused!
Huh?
Combining is a long way off.
I'm gonna head to school.
Bye!
In an instant of time,
the arrow in flight is stationary.
Fujiyokidai High School
The duration of flight
consists of all those instants.
Remember, photos are due today—
Oh. Where you headed?
Music room. Coming?
Huh? Uh, sure.
Got work today?
Yeah.
Are you in a hurry?
No. It's a late start.
I see.
What's at the music room?
Chorus club.
Kano... I mean, my big sister was in it.
Oh, yeah?
I thought I'd ask around
and see what I learn.
Yeah, I was the club advisor
five years ago,
but I can't remember much
about your sister.
I see.
Oh, but Kanae might know.
Huh?
She was like the life of the chorus club at the time.
She keeps in touch.
Would she know about my sister?
I would think so.
Could we meet her?
Um, yeah. She'll probably help out.
Wait a sec and I'll try to reach her.
Thank you.
Nice. You'll get to meet her.
Yeah.
My sister...
She died just before
a recital five years ago.
We didn't exactly interact a whole lot.
We spoke as little as we had to.
Yeah.
But that recital was the first
she ever invited me to.
I always wonder why she invited me.
I see.
Are you late?
Hello, Yomo?
Still not here?
STILL?
Ranka
Awaki
kmkr excursion
Yeah, I should go.
Thanks for coming along.
Yeah, later.
#kaiju#scary#crazy#
downfall#crazy videos...
#whatthehell#kaiju?#
terrible#appea
Kaiju and robots.
We live in dangerous times.
Someone I know from club said
their neighborhood got wrecked.
Yomogi doesn't even seem to care.
No, that's not true.
Hello.
Do you have a moment?
Uh, sure.
Who's that?
Yomogi's been with
some weird people lately.
Ugh, I'm starving.
Who's that?
A chorus club grad.
Chorus club?
I got their number from the advisor
when I asked about my sister.
Huh? To meet them?
Yeah.
Will you be okay, Yume? All by yourself?
Shut up, Mom.
Huh? Koyomi?
It is you! Long time no see!
Not since middle school, right?
Uh, yeah.
You're still in the area?
Yeah, kinda.
You work nearby?
Hmm? You could say that.
I... help people in need.
That's amazing!
Nah, it's nothing special.
I moved back here after getting married.
Married?
Yeah. A while ago.
Yeah? I see... Marriage, huh? Yeah.
Congratulations.
Thank you. But I think
you're late by a long shot.
Koyomi, are you marri—?
No, not yet.
Any girlfriends?
Not at the moment.
Oh! Why don't we exchange contact info?
Okay.
Senpai.
Whoa!
Is that your ex?
No way.
Thought so. You've never
dated anyone, right?
Huh?
Do you still like her?
It's not like that.
It is like that.
Sorry for pulling you away
from your friends.
Uh, it's okay, um...
It's Juuga.
Yomogi Asanaka.
Yomogi, I'd just like to talk a bit.
Right.
Um, you said you used to be comrades
with Gauma before, right?
Yes. Gauma was someone
I looked up to... 5,000 years ago.
We died 5,000 years ago and were
revived in this era... for some reason.
Kinda boggles the mind.
It sure does.
If you used to be comrades,
why aren't you together?
That's something you should ask him.
I need to get to work. Sorry.
Oh. Thanks for your time.
The hell was that for, Juuga?
We kill the kid and it's over.
If they're Kaiju users,
why not have them as comrades?
Comrades?!
Dynazenon... None of us
could control that phoney kaiju.
It's not a kaiju.
Who cares?! Let's just
crush the hell outta Gauma!
Hey, Freshman. About your no-show...
W-Well... Yeah, I'm sorry.
What happened?
I was, uh... helping people in need.
Is that some sort of new trend?
Why are we meeting up so late?
Someone's gonna call child protection.
There's an adult, so we're fine.
An unemployed one.
Oh, me?
Unemployed...
I've got Dynazenon now, so...
So, what's this about?
I spoke with Juuga today.
Who?
One of the Kaiju users from before?
Yeah. Gauma and them died 5,000 years ago
and were revived in this era.
Five thousand years...
Revived...
Kaiju users...
A bit much?
I don't know what to tell you.
Anyway, he said that Gauma betrayed them.
Between this Juuga guy
and Gauma, who do you trust?
Neither, honestly.
Good point.
Five thousand years...
Well, why don't we just ask him in person?
Where does he live?
Gauma! Hello?!
What do you want?
What's that you're eating?
Crabs from around here.
Uh...
What do you want?
Um, you and the Kaiju Eugenicists
used to be comrades, right?
Yeah, 5,000 years ago.
See? 5,000 years! See?
And what of it?
We heard that you betrayed them.
Huh? I guess you could say that.
But why?
In order to stop those guys.
They're psychos who
carry out the will of kaiju.
So, you betrayed them to protect people?
Would you give it a rest?
You don't need to know.
Yeah, but—!
Sorry, but I've got the night shift.
You got a job?
Gotta feed myself.
Do you think he just
likes fighting in robots?
Maybe. What if he's actually a psycho?
Well, he is a psycho.
He was eating those crabs.
What's he fighting for?
Is there some reason for it?
Hmm.
Do you think he's hiding something?
Please don't crowd around—
There it is!
It's a good one! Care if I go for it?!
Go right ahead.
Instance Domination!
Boom! Boom!
Do we have to cooperate with Gauma
if another Kaiju shows up?
Probably.
Yeah?
There's a Kaiju in Chiba!
Huh? A kaiju?
He hung up.
What now?
What now? We can't just head to Chiba
during the middle of school.
Wrong.
Huh?
The afternoon has gym, homeroom,
and other dumb classes.
It might be doable.
Let's go.
Right.
I'm going to Chiba.
Why Chiba? Like, a kaiju?
Gauma.
Huh?
Do you fight to protect people?
Would you give it up already?
Now that's a lovely sight!
Eh?
There you are, Gauma!
This time, I'll crush you!
No, I'll blast you to bits!
Here goes! Commence attack!
That was a close one!
I can't even get close.
Talk about a Kaiju with an annoying power!
Let's combine and fight!
Combine?
We can't combine without—
Wrong! If our feelings are one,
we can do it!
No...
Why?
We'll never unite our feelings.
What?
Gauma, are you not telling us something?
You guys...!
Gauma, tell us the truth!
Fine, but let's do this later!
We want to know now!
I'll blow you to bits, you phoney kaiju!
Listen up, Yomogi.
In this world, there're three things
important for people to keep:
You said that before!
Promises, love, and...!
You thought your phoney kaiju
stood a chance against me?!
I totally blew you to bits!
You moron! We almost died
'cuz all of your yapping!
It's 'cuz you're not answering!
Just tell us and we can move on!
Are we falling?
You're too heavy!
What the—?!
We want to know about you, Gauma!
Yomogi...
There's a reason you're fighting, right?!
Tell us what it is! Now!
Right now?
Please!
Fine.
There's someone I wanna meet.
Huh?
The one who entrusted Dynazenon to me.
I was given this power, so that
in this era, I could find that person.
Is this other person a guy?
A woman.
Ah...
Sorry for keeping quiet!
But please, fight with me!
Only Dynazenon can defeat Kaiju!
Yomogi, Yume, Koyomi...
Right now, I need you guys!
Right!
Thank you!
Combine Dragon Dynazenon!
You fools combining
doesn't change a thing!
You're about to get a taste of
our full, combined power!
Dyna Saber!
Dammit!
These damn explosions!
What if there was no fire?
If there was a place without air...!
Where's a place like that?!
Oh. Can't Dynazenon fly?
It might be doable!
Let's go!
Up?!
Back then, our four hearts connected!
Let's combine our feelings as one again!
So we can beat this guy!
Dynazenon!
Battle, Go!
Shit!
It was worth the trip up here!
This time, it's our turn!
Dynazenon Full Burst!
We did it!
Wait!
It ain't over yet!
Super Dragon Dyna Rex!
Rex Fang!
I died 5,000 years ago
and was revived in this era, so...
The person you wanna meet
could've revived, too?
Yeah.
I've been looking for them,
believing someday, we'd meet again.
Maybe the only reason
we revived was because
Kaiju defy common sense.
The power of Kaiju makes
the impossible possible, right?
Like, reviving people...
I thought I was dead.