We lost.
Dynazenon beat us.
I see. And that kaiju even
destroyed time and space.
People seeing their past and future
should've spawned lots of emotions.
However...
Kaiju aren't appearing.
Meaning all the kaiju seeds
were wiped out.
So, kaiju won't be born anymore?
We were beaten.
We lost to Gauma?
Their weapon isn't from this era.
It had to come from 5,000 years ago.
If there's no kaiju,
I'll just kill people myself.
There has to be something we can do
for the world of kaiju.
For all the kaiju that have fallen.
Kaiju users without kaiju
return to human beings?
Like Gauma.
Senpai, what are you doing?
Making a resume.
Huh?
I wonder if I need a suit?
Uh... Where'd it go?
Hey, Mom! Have you seen my suit?
You're kidding me.
This is from my mom.
Hmm? Thanks.
Crab crisps from Toyosu.
Tastes better than river crabs.
Tsk! Shaddap!
Get moving or you'll be late.
Yeah.
Ugh, I feel like shit.
What's wrong with me?
Huh? You apologized to the 2nd-year?
After all this time.
What are you doing?
Picking an entry for the festival.
Yeah?
Can I use one with you in it?
Hell no.
So, no more Sizumu?
Really?
Could be family issues.
He wasn't very friendly.
I look so weird in this.
Watch over me, Goldburn!
I can't do it after all.
Chise?
Huh?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, but what's this about?
--Goldburn.
--Hmm?
Soon, we'll be leaving here for good.
That's sudden.
Kaiju shouldn't appear anymore.
We and Goldburn are irregulars here.
Which is why we're
taking Goldburn with us.
Why?
A world without kaiju
is much more natural.
Prepare your heart.
I know that's the way things should be.
I know, but...
I just don't get it!
Gauma seems out of it lately.
Without his spunk, he's boring.
Right?
Worried about him?
Not exactly.
You are.
I knew this day would eventually come.
Both Senpai... and you... are leaving me.
What do you want?
If you're here to fight, bring it on.
No, it seems kaiju won't be
appearing anymore.
We lost.
I came to tell you--
Don't think saying that changes anything!
Do you even know the things
that you've done?!
It's about time I teach you!
Gauma! What are you doing?!
Cut it out!
Violence is bad!
Don't ever show your face again!
That was my plan.
It's actually sad how little
your punches hurt. That hasn't changed.
Kaiju won't appear anymore?
Is that why you're feeling down?
Huh? Did it look that way?
Seems like you're out of it lately. Ow.
When I revived, I thought Princess would,
too, somewhere in the world.
Princess?
The person you're searching for
is a princess?
Yeah. We vowed to
spend our future together.
Which is why after I died,
Princess ended her own life.
Huh?
How do you know
what happened after you died?
I heard it.
Princess died so she could meet you!
She followed you into death!
"She wanted to give you this."
Whose voice was it?
I can't remember,
but Princess had a premonition.
She knew I'd need Dynazenon in the future.
But only the kaiju users
were revived, so Princess...
You won't get to meet her?
Who knows?
But I'm glad I came to this place.
The scenery's so similar.
I doubt we'll need Dynazenon anymore.
I had Koyomi return his.
You going somewhere?
I just might.
What's up?
Nothing. But now that I look at it,
he's actually kinda cool.
"Photo Dispenser"
Nothing. But now that I look at it,
he's actually kinda cool.
I look awful.
Wh-What?!
I thought I'd come tell you myself.
There probably won't be more kaiju.
I heard.
So, no more fighting.
I see.
But it's not like I can say
everything's just dandy now.
Kaiju have changed me
and everything around me.
Do you despise me?
No. You were just doing the duty
you were meant to do.
Well, I despise you.
There it is.
What's that? A mirror?
A 5,000-year-old mirror went missing.
The mirror came to life and vanished?
I'm thinking it might be Gauma.
The mirror? Freaky.
How'd he come back to life?
A kaiju's power?
Probably.
Princess wasn't a kaiju user,
so she didn't revive.
And because of that, they'll never meet.
Must be why he's so bummed.
Yeah.
Yomogi, can you come with me
somewhere tomorrow?
Tomorrow, I'm planning
to visit Kano's grave.
That seems sudden.
I guess it is.
When are you going?
Huh?
Need a ride?
No, I'll be fine on my own.
What? I said we're eating
with Kamijo tomorrow.
Sorry.
We scheduled around you.
Sorry!
Sorry doesn't cut it.
You can eat out whenever,
so what's the big deal?
Eh?
"interview questions"
"Search Results for: suits haircut grooming"
"Search Results for: interview questions"
"What are my strengths?"
Make sure you thank him
for all he's done for us, Knight.
I know.
What's with the early visit?
We came to say goodbye
since we'll be leaving soon.
Thanks for everything.
I see. Thanks for your help. Be safe.
Knight!
Thanks for everything.
Couldn't hear you.
C'mon! Say it even louder!
"Minami Family Grave"
Flowers facing this way?
That's fine.
I've never visited Kano till now.
You haven't?
"Minami"
I kept avoiding it.
My mom was a bit surprised,
but my dad actually looked glad.
I swear, my parents drive me nuts.
You don't have that problem, do you?
Well, the thing is...
Mmm?
A dude I don't know might become my dad.
Yeah?
Though, he's not a bad guy.
We've both got it rough. Oh!
I'll tell my ancestors
all my parents do is fight.
Seriously?
Kidding!
"Minami"
I've never visited someone else's grave.
I thought if anyone,
maybe you would understand.
I'll return these.
R-Right.
Thanks.
Isn't this nearby?
What?
He punched a cop
and tried to take his gun.
That'll do it.
What a crazy look.
Let's see.
"Self-Proclaimed 'Kaiju Eugenicist'"
"Suspect Name: Onija
Age: 5021 (Claimed)"
"Self-Proclaimed 'Kaiju Eugenicist'"
"Suspect Name: Onija
Age: 5021 (Claimed)"
So cool!
Looks bad over there.
It's where the first one appeared.
You brought me there, right?
Yeah.
Kaiju appeared all over the place, huh?
We fought kaiju and stuff,
but it was the closest to normal
my life's ever been.
Normal? How is that normal?
The piloting a robot part wasn't normal.
But visiting graves, going swimming,
missing the festival
and doing fireworks...
That happened.
If there's no kaiju and
we're done with Dynazenon,
won't we not see everyone?
Is my "normal" done for, too?
Deep inside, maybe you just
want to fight them?
Maybe Sizumu was right when he said--
Minami.
Hmm?
Even if there's no kaiju...
Even if there's no Dynazenon...
...I still want to see you.
Yeah.
I like you. Will you go out with me?
I was right to hang around you two.
--Huh?
--Sizumu?
Now I get why Gauma died
as a kaiju user and became a human.
Because he's just like you two.
Gauma!
Gauma...
Wait. What are you doing?
I knew you'd show up. You've had
your eyes on 'em for a while.
I'm grateful to you two. You helped me
witness some wonderful emotions.
Thank you.
Gauma, your body!
We revived with the power of kaiju,
defying the laws of the world.
But being a human,
your body will decay and you'll die.
Since we're connected to kaiju,
that won't happen to us.
Wish you would've told me from the start.
If I had, would you have
become a kaiju user?
Quit asking stupid questions.
The fighting is over, Eugenicist!
You lost all your kaiju!
I never lose my kaiju.
Instance...
...Domination!
No way! He's...!
There's a kaiju inside him?!
Kaiju deserve to be free.
Sizumu turned into a kaiju?!
What's wrong?
I see. Don't worry about me. Go!
"New Kaiju Spotted in Tokyo"
Those in the area
should take extreme caution.
Kaiju?
Goldburn!
Call Koyomi. We'll stop him
with Dynazenon.
But you're in no shape for that!
Let me handle this.
If I use Goldburn, I can combine
into Dynazenon without any help.
Even so...
Wait here.
Super Dragon King Kaiser Gridknight!
Knight's holding the kaiju back.
Let's get to the hospital!
The hospital can't fix this.
Sitting here won't help either!
Gauma?
Hey, hey... I thought I was dead.
The world of kaiju isn't over just yet!
"Episode 11: What Wish Can't Come True?"