Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realize your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
When I met you, you were all alone
I want to know why you were looking so lorn
Stand proud!
It all depends on us!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Um, Captain?
Yomo? Minami?
Senpai...
Huh?
What's this?
Huh?! N-No way!
Hey! Turn this back to normal!
Wh-Whoa!
It's all back...
You understand me.
Sit.
Lie down.
Paw.
Not quite, but whatever.
You need a name, don't you?
Um, let's give you a cool one.
All right. Your name will be Goldburn.
What Are These Overlapping Emotions?
— Episode 9 —
Going to the festival, Yomogi?
There's fireworks.
Super crummy ones.
You going?
38th
Uzukigaoka
Fireworks
Festival
I can't make it.
It's my brother's birthday.
I've got plans to go eat.
Me, too.
Why don't you two go?
No way.
Not interested in the festival?
Huh? Uh, not really.
I think I wanna go.
Huh? Should we check it out?
Mmm.
I'll ask the others
since I bet they're bored.
Think Knight will come?
Hmm. Don't know.
Oh. No way to reach him.
Just let me know.
Okay.
Senpai.
Hmm?
Hypothetically, if there was
a peaceful kaiju that understood—
Oh, sorry. Hello?
Hey, Yomogi.
Festival?
I've got nothing going on.
Yeah.
I'll see if Chise—
Huh?
Model Apartments Open
Ugh, I'm spent.
Captain Gauma.
Hmm? What's up?
Hypothetically...
Model Apartments Open
Just hypothetically...
If there was a peaceful kaiju
that understood people, what then?
You're thinking about
that last kaiju, huh?
We've gotta fight any kaiju
that poses a threat.
That's our duty.
A-Absolutely!
Shoot. I've gotta keep Goldburn
a secret. If anyone finds—
Wh-What?! What?!
No, no, no! Too big, too big! Shrink, Goldburn!
Go back to being small!
Like before! Much smaller than—
You're not listening at all.
Awesome!
Huh?
The lousy Ayame Middle School...
Huh?! Goldburn?!
W-Wait, wait! No!
I almost became like a Kaiju Eugenicist.
Sorry, Goldburn.
38th
Uzukigaoka
Fireworks
Festival
Yomogi!
Mmm?
You've got a guest.
Huh?
I'm Futaba Senda, the chorus club grad.
Any progress?
With what?
You guys dating?
Shut up.
Hello?
Minami? Futaba just showed up here.
Huh?
Um, all right.
Sorry, I've gotta go back.
Why?
I'm super sorry.
The boyfriend, huh?!
Ex-boyfriend!
That girl...
I've got this one.
It does seem right up your alley.
You've got this.
Instance Domination.
I heard from my old work
that you guys were looking for me.
Sorry to bother you.
You're Kano's little sister, right?
Yeah. Yume Minami.
Is it true that you two were dating?
Yeah, we were at the time.
So, you knew that she was
being bullied in chorus club?
I heard rumors about it,
but I never saw it in person.
Besides, people don't just
admit they're being bullied.
That's true...
But it made Kano commit suicide.
No. Even the police
concluded it was an accident.
I wonder... was it really?
Kano wasn't like that.
She wouldn't kill herself.
Sorry, I've gotta get going.
Okay.
Bye.
Why?
If you were dating Kano,
why didn't you save her?!
Yeah, most people would think that.
What's that mean?
Minami—
A kaiju? At a time like this?
Let's go, Yomogi.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Let's hurry.
R-Right.
Sorry, go on ahead. I'll be right there.
But!
I'm fine, really.
Go.
All right.
What now?
When you're this big,
I can't bring you home.
Another kaiju?!
Huh?
H-Hey! Wait! Wait up, Goldburn!
Dyna Launcher Burst Missile!
Shit! The ground!
We can't fight this alone!
Where the hell are Yomogi and Yume?!
With this kaiju, I can beat Gauma at last!
You know...
Don't get too worked up.
We have a guest.
Be careful out there, Knight.
Having trouble, Gauma?
The whole team's not here yet!
Gauma!
You're late, Yomogi!
Hey, where's Yume?
She'll probably be here shortly.
What's "probably"?! What happened to her?
About that...
She met with her sister's ex
and was acting a bit strange.
And? You just ditched her?
No, I left because—
Hey!
Go get Yume right now!
Huh?
What have you been around her for?!
You can tell that she's acting strange!
I-I... I'll go get her!
Come back together.
You're the only one who can bring her back!
Right!
If there's something
only I can do, I've gotta do it.
It's no use. I totally lost him.
Hmm?
Minami?
What are you doing here?
Isn't there a kaiju?
Um, shouldn't you be helping?
I know. I know that.
What's the matter?
I'm fine. I'm fine, and it's got
nothing to do with you.
When I fight, nothing good
ever comes from it.
I wish you wouldn't say that.
I try to fight as part of
the team, you know.
So don't say it's got
nothing to do with me!
A kaiju?!
No, that's—!
Minami!
Minami! You okay?!
Yomogi...
I came... to get you.
Minami, are you sure
nothing good came from it?
This guy charged in to save you.
Is there anyone else
that would do that for you?
You don't know what you've got.
Minami!
Huh?
Kano...
The kaiju... saved her?
That's Goldburn, my friend!
A friend... kaiju?
Knight Bursting Light Bom—
Knight!
I-I can't move!
Shit! We're screwed!
Gauma! I will now surpass you!
We're really sinking!
Yomogi! Where are you?!
Gauma!
Sorry we're late!
You're late as hell, you two!
Huh? What's going on?
What's up with that kaiju?
What's wrong?
I can't control it. No, it's rejecting me.
This kaiju can hear my heart!
Your heart?
Captain! Please trust this kaiju!
Chise's telling the truth!
It saved us!
This kaiju is my friend!
If Chise says so, it must be true.
All right. Since I believe in you guys,
I'll believe in the kaiju, too!
Combine Dragon Dynazenon!
Go, Goldburn!
What?!
Let's save him while we're at it!
I didn't need help.
Don't get me wrong. It wasn't to help you.
Quit with the flirting.
I'll wipe you both out at once!
Goldburn has the power
to protect everyone!
It's time to put our powers together!
Right!
Super Dragon King Kaiser Gridknight!
What the hell is that?!
All of 'em lumped together.
The giant, Dynazenon,
and kaiju became one.
That still doesn't mean
you're gonna beat me!
So fast!
And strong!
We've got this!
Yeah!
This is the power of all of us together!
Kaiser Knight Double Storm!
Shoot!
Yomogi Asanaka!
Dynamic Cannon!
Rex...
...Grid...
...Fire!
Well, you almost had it, Juuga.
We'll win next time, yeah?
There's not an infinite number
of kaiju, you know.
That's true.
I realized something today.
We've all gotta fight together.
We can't win without everyone.
Even me?
Including you... and Goldburn.
We're too late for the festival.
No, not if we run.
All right!
Right now?
C'mon, get moving!
You guys, too.
We didn't make it.
Guess not.
Who wants to do fireworks?
Huh?
Like, our own.
That's a great idea!
We'll go and buy some!
Huh? Okay.
I wanna buy some, too!
Huh? O-Okay.
Can I go home for a sec?
What for?
I'll be right back.
You were looking a little downcast and I wanted to have a chat
So I tried walking a whole step closer alongside you
Minami sure is late.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Late, yet again?
I'll go get her.
The shadows were growing like a sundial's needle at sunset
You were striding so fast I thought the season'd change
Sorry for taking so long.
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Just like your smiling face