Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realize your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
When I met you, you were all alone
I want to know why you were looking so lorn
Stand proud!
It all depends on us!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Here I go!
Perfect!
Nice, Chise! Really good form!
Senpai, this is pretty easy!
It's easy, huh?
She's a quick learner.
Um, I've got a question.
What?
Dyna Soldier and Dyna Wing
can combine, right?
Yup.
So, can't it do the same thing
with Koyomi's Dyna Striker?
Good point. Wanna try?
Huh? You mean, today?
Okay! Take over, Yomo!
Huh? Uh, I'm doing it?
Ugh. I kinda wanted to leave early...
Then hurry it up.
Dyna Soldier Striker Combine!
There. We did it.
That's pretty slick!
I'd call it a success!
Uh, careful! Whoa!
That hurt.
Yeah. Might be a balance problem
if it can't even stand.
All right! Try again!
Sorry, but I've gotta go soon!
Eh?
Oh. Me, too.
Ah, I guess you're right.
Yeah. I've got plans.
Even you?
I told you I was taking today off!
And yet, here I am!
What's a day off to the unemployed?
Fine! That's it for today! Disperse!
What's Lover-Like Mean?
— Episode 5 —
Sorry. All I have is the edited version,
so it might not have what you want.
[Vlog #27] Sopranos
It's okay. Thank you.
This video isn't public. No one can see it
unless they have the link.
Yeah?
There's lots of footage of people
goofing off, so we hid it from the school.
It won't show up in searches.
I see.
She's smiling a lot.
Um...
What?
Is it okay for us to drink together?
Huh?
Aren't you married, Inamoto?
I guess I am!
You know, Inamoto isn't
my last name anymore.
And yet, it's okay to drink with me?
Come on! Of course, it's fine!
Yeah?
I wonder why I got married?
Koyomi, you haven't told anyone
my secret, right?
I haven't.
It'd be bad if the school
learned I broke the glass.
Yeah, probably.
I might get expelled.
Middle schoolers can't be, right?
Oh, yeah. Wanna see something neat?
Cho Jin
Public
Izakaya
Thanks for today.
Mmm.
Till next time! See ya!
C'mon, Senpai.
Forget the women of the past.
Why are you here?
Wanna see something neat?
Neat?
Ta-da! This girl won free tickets
to Tokyo Beach Land!
Congratulations!
Tokyo Beach Land
Free Entry
Winner!
Fujiyokidai High School
Sizumu is the enemy, right?
Yeah. He is to Gauma at least.
What's our relationship with a classmate
who's a Kaiju Eugenicist?
Relationship, huh?
Ask her out on a date.
It's not that easy.
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
I won tickets to Tokyo Beach Land!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Chise
Winner!
Let's hit the pool this weekend!
Chise
I won tickets to Tokyo
Beach Land! Let's hit the
pool this weekend!
Winner!
The pool? What do you think?
Hmm.
Um, shouldn't we go?
Sounds nice.
Huh?
The pool. Think I can come?
Um...
Sure.
Huh?
Let's all go.
Thanks.
You're right. It might be
a good chance to capture Sizumu.
Yume, you're a genius!
I figured we should work together.
I see.
I couldn't get him at school,
but this time, I'll nab him for sure.
Captain Gauma, do you have a plan for it?
I do!
Like?
Like...
Like this!
But first, dinner! Eat up! You can't
do squat on an empty stomach!
Senpai, do you have a swimsuit?
That jerk is never gonna see it coming.
I have one from elementary school.
Huh? Does it fit?
This time, I'll get him for sure!
It fits.
Well, whatever.
From elementary school?
Like, bam!
TOKYO BEACH LAND
It's Sunday!
And yet, it's totally dead.
'Cuz it's June.
Gauma, your face!
Which arm do I wear the key on?
Uh, I don't think it matters.
I'm gonna get payback, big time.
Hmm. All right.
I'm gonna nab you this time.
Gauma, we hear you!
Do you swim often?
Nah, I'm not that good at it.
Mmm?
What?
We'll catch him off guard. You two can
pretend to be lovers, so act natural.
Huh?
That's the opposite of natural!
Don't let him see through you.
R-Right.
Good. May the operation to capture
a Kaiju Eugenicist begin!
Act like lovers... How?
Where do we start?
Huh?
Yeah. How long should we
say we've dated for?
What?
Huh? Uh, never mind.
Let's start with a small one!
Unlike school, no one will
get in my way here.
Prepare yourself, Sizumu! Here I come—!
No running by the pool!
Huh? Eating already?
I didn't have breakfast.
Churro?
The sugar's getting everywhere.
Is it good?
Mmm.
Oh, Sizumu. Huh? Where's Gauma?
Getting yelled at for running.
That's embarrassing.
Go ahead, you two.
Don't wait on me.
Huh?
Let's go, Yomogi.
Yeah, sure... Uh...
Wanna do that?
Mmm.
It looks empty. C'mon.
Oh, wait.
Huh?
You shouldn't run.
Good point. Don't wanna get yelled at.
Just put your trust in me it's gonna work out, alright
Look! Inner tubes!
I can convince you even if it's gonna take all night
Yeah, let's.
Cos there's something in my mind I can picture inside me
It took away my breath and my heart is beating faster
Its chemistry at work whenever we're together
The sign
Something tells me that you're gonna fall
Those two are hitting it off.
Sure are. Say, where's Gauma?
For my charms and my affection
Uh... I wonder if his strategy succeeded?
Move in my direction
Let me show
I'm never wrong
Look at you, lounging around.
I can tell the situation's
I'm so gonna capture you!
The one that we've been waiting
Just as planned, I'm gonna—
All this time, I know
No jumping, please!
Dammit, Sizumu! Screw you!
You okay?
Don't worry. The operation
is just getting started.
You look a little beat up.
Wanna relax in the onsen?
Whoa! I almost fell!
Hey! Quit shaking it!
Can you make it?
Yeah, probably.
Don't knock me off, jeez!
Sorry, my bad!
Minami?
Sorry, I'm heading back.
Huh?
Sorry. Did I tire you out from
running around too much?
No, it's not your fault.
By the way, I wonder how
Gauma's strategy is going.
Strategy?
Huh?
All right, that's better. I'm revived.
This time, I'll—
This guy isn't built very strong.
Uh, I said "strategy," but...
I mean, like, an "everyone-get-along
strategy" or something...
Yeah, you know?
Sorry. Forget I said anything.
Are you two dating?
Huh? Um, us... dating?
People like to give themselves
purpose like that.
Purpose?
They seek freedom while also
constraining themselves.
They influence others while being
influenced themselves. Isn't that sad?
I wouldn't say I feel constrained.
That's only because you guys
can't see your own prisons.
Right.
Why did you approach us?
Like I said before, I was curious.
Because we pilot Dynazenon?
There's that, but I felt
emotions from you.
Emotions?
Emotions are a kaiju's favorite thing.
Kaiju have favorites?
Ah! There you are!
You're up, Sizumu!
Well, see you later.
We're leaving already? We just got here.
Are you kidding me?
We're about to wreck shit up!
Can we come back after?!
You're welcome to.
What was that about?
Yomogi! Were they just here?!
Yeah. They left pretty quickly.
I wonder if they won tickets, too?
Kaiju?!
What is that thing? So creepy.
Well, Sizumu?
Yeah. It's not bad.
Instance Domination.
Hurry up, but don't run!
There's no time to change!
Access Mode... Dyna Soldier!
Dyna Wing!
Dyna Striker!
Dyna Diver!
Oh. I left Chise behind.
Huh?! Chise?!
I kinda climbed aboard out of habit.
Oh. Out of habit, huh?
They got here quick.
Let's combine and wrap this up!
Not on my watch.
C'mon! Hey!
Quit picking on Yume!
Argh, shit!
Minami!
If only I could attack from afar!
Oh, Koyomi! Let's try that thing!
Huh? Are you sure?
Please!
Senpai!
All right!
Dyna Soldier Striker Combine!
You can do it, Yomogi!
Hang in there, Dyna Soldier!
Striker Storm Alpha!
Striker Storm Beta!
Fire!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ouch!
All right! Time to combine!
Combine Dragon Dynazenon!
There's Dynazenon! Crush 'em, Sizumu!
Dynazenon...
...Battle, Go!
Hey, hey, hey! The hell is this thing?!
Disperse!
What?!
Super Dragon Dyna Rex!
Blazing Inferno...
...Rex Roar!
I lost.
Can we go back?!
Uh, sure.
Aren't you guys pissed?!
Gauma may have won again,
but next time, we're gonna whoop his a—
I wanted to swim more!
Sizumu's gonna get it next time.
We've gotta go back and get our stuff.
Oh! We can swim more while we're there!
My strategy was too sloppy.
I've had enough.
Aww!
Thanks for back there.
Huh?
No jumping, please!
It's freezing!
Minami! You, too!
Aww!
Today
Urita
I got a hold of Fuuma, the club
vice-president. Want me to put
you in touch?
TOKYO BEACH LAND
The onsen, at last!
I thought I was dead.
I heard from Urita that you
want to know about Kano?
Yes. I'm curious about what happened
before her accident.
About that...
What is it?
It's hard to say in front of
her little sister.
Don't worry about it.
It's been five years.
I see.
If you know something, please say.
It's just a rumor I heard
back then, but...
Yeah?
It wasn't an accident, but suici—
You were looking a little downcast and I wanted to have a chat
So I tried walking a whole step closer alongside you
The shadows were growing like a sundial's needle at sunset
You were striding so fast I thought the season'd change
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Just like your smiling face