Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realize your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
When I met you, you were all alone
I want to know why you were looking so lorn
Stand proud!
It all depends on us!
We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness
And all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed right now!
Suicide...
Like I said, it's just a rumor.
A rumor...
Kano was cheerful and everyone loved her,
but that attitude slowly changed.
Did something happen?
I think Futaba was the main reason.
Futaba?
Yeah... Didn't Kano tell you?
I've never heard of him.
I see.
Well, we didn't talk about those things.
Futaba Senda, the club's vice president.
He had a way with people—
knew how to charm 'em.
I think a lot of the girls liked him.
Sooner or later, he and Kano
became a thing.
Hold up a sec. You're saying Kano
was going out with this guy?
Emergency Exit
Yeah. And he kept pushing the song
Kano picked out for the recital.
Maybe the girls were involved.
It started with playful teasing, but...
Huh?
What do you mean? They bullied her?
I don't know if they did or not,
but it felt like there might've
been something.
In the video Urita showed us,
it didn't seem that way at all.
Yeah.
The unlisted videos aren't
the only ones out there.
Huh?
Some were made private
after Kano's accident.
That's something I've gotta see!
Yeah, all right. I can share 'em
with your account.
Please do.
Sorry for dragging you around.
Nah. I decided to tag along on my own.
Thanks.
What's up?
It feels like...
I never knew Kano at all.
What Is This Pain?
— Episode 6 —
You think that's what happened?
What will you do?
If it's true she didn't die by accident,
I want to find out why.
If it was bullying,
there won't be proof. It's bullying.
You might not like what you learn
if you look into it.
Even so, I've decided to think positive
and learn more about her.
Think positive...
Yes.
Atta girl!
Too close!
I was wrong about you!
Thanks.
That's the spirit!
If we don't think positive—
It won't be easy
winning Gauma to our side.
Since they'll keep interfering,
shall we just kill them?
Changing your mind?
That's what I said from the start.
What do you think, Mujina?
I'll do whatever we decide.
I'm against it.
Why's that?
Dynazenon might be why
kaiju keep appearing.
It's easy enough to kill those guys,
but I wanna meet more kaiju first.
There's no rush?
It'll be fine. The world is
heading in a good direction.
What's up? You okay?
Not really.
No, huh?
A girl I know...
She's confronting something tough
by not running away.
Yeah, it's here.
You sure about this?
Check it out. Neat, huh?
Whose could it be?
I wasn't sure what to do
when I found this,
but I wanted to show you at least.
Uh... Th-This is a bad idea.
Huh? It's fine.
No one else knows it's here.
S-Sorry!
Hmm?
U-Um...
Maybe she's right...
What's bright?
Bright! Brighter than the sun!
Hmm? Hey!
Hey.
Huh?
I had him swing by since he was close.
This is Arata. Uh, my husband.
Oh. You're...
Hello. I'm Arata Tachibana.
I run a shop in Sanae. Nice to meet you.
Uh, hello.
Tiny table for three.
Sure is.
She always talks about you, Yamamoto.
Yamanaka.
Whoops. Sorry.
It's fine.
You've known her
since middle school, right?
Was she always like this?
Huh?
Having hometown pals is great.
I still hang out with my old crew, too.
Can we add tomatoes and skewers?
I haven't played futsal lately.
Last week—
Do you work nearby, Yamamoto?
It's been fun. Thanks for coming.
Let's hang out again.
Y-Yeah.
Someday, yeah.
Senpai's late.
What is this?
Yamamoto... Yamamoto... Yamamoto...
Who the hell's Yamamoto?
You're kidding!
Oh, my umbrella... I forgot it.
Oh, shoot. Is that the enemy lady, or not?
In that outfit, it's gotta be her.
But Gauma's not here, so why mess with me?
Then again, she was staring. But I'm not—
Oh. You're the Dynazenon—
K-Kaiju Eugenicist?!
That's right.
I'm starving.
Are you... gonna... eat me?!
Are you drunk?
Lately, Yomogi's made
some interesting friends!
Is that right?
Like the one who came to eat with us.
Um, his name was...
Gauma?
Gauma!
You're so loud.
He seems like such a good guy!
Doesn't he have a job doing something?
He's working part-time.
Yeah?
Part-time?
Yomogi's working, too!
Well, a girlfriend doesn't come cheap!
I really hope he brings one home soon.
Just so we're on the same page,
I don't have any money.
I realize that.
I don't have to pay?
Give it a rest.
Why complain about marriage
and lead me on?
And then invite your husband?
What the hell?
What am I even doing?
Beats me.
Can't you phrase it a better way?
I don't know anything about you, Koyomi.
I don't even know much about myself.
Unlike other people, I have nothing
I want to do. At all.
Well, I don't either!
In that case, we're the same.
Finally.
Pre-Recital Pranking!!
~Kanokano Edition~
Minami! Come on in!
She closed it!
Where are you going?
Come back!
Hey, Minami. Did you lose something?
Did you lose something?
Huh? What do you mean? Um, I don't know.
I don't know
Well, maybe you should look.
Kanokano's searching
Oh. My ankh puzzle's gone.
My ankh puzzle's gone.
My ankh puzzle's...
go
ne
She got it!!!!!!
Oh no! Look for it!
That voice...
Kano-Kano is searching the clubroom
C'mon!
It's raining, so hurry up!
Can't you give a hint?
I did! I just did!
Kanokano missed the hint
But then...
Kanokano sees something
Oh, did you find it?!
That was quick!
Ta-da!
Ankh puzzle
found! !
Just so you know,
we didn't throw it. We put it here.
Thank goodness
Prank... success!
Prank success!!
Subscribe if you liked it!
Recommended Videos
Click below
(Title)
Subscribe
But everyone loved her
'cuz she was cheerful.
Prank... success!
She really paid for it...
Hey!
It shouldn't be like this...
Why is it always like this?
I had money... I had tons of it.
Kano's death wasn't an accident?
Yomo!
Where've you been?
He's just avoiding us.
I've been busy.
Working too much?
You haven't handed this in?
Cut it out! Give it back!
Tiny letters!
It wouldn't fit!
Who needs two rows?
Yomoguilty!
Yomoguilty?
Senpai, you drinking
with married women again?
Who cares?
Ugh, I feel sick!
Aren't you going to training today?
No, there's no way.
Tell Gauma I can't make it.
All right. But if you're not going,
lend me Dyna Striker.
I'll go in your place.
Huh?
Hmm?
It's gone.
What?! You lost Dyna Striker?!
S-Sorry.
Forgive him, please.
He feels bad about it.
So?! Where and when did you lose it?!
Uh, well...
He was drunk and can't remember.
You can't just lose something like that!
It was stolen... by Mujina.
Huh?
Mujina?!
What should I do with this?
Hey, hey, hey! It's a slice of Dynazenon!
Steal it?
Mmm.
Nice work! Let's use it and wreck shit up!
No, it's a valuable weapon of the enemy's.
We could use it to
negotiate with Gauma and—
No. Let's give it back.
It's not ours.
What do you think, Mujina?
Huh?
I...
Dynazenon is one body split into four.
Oh?
My Dyna Diver can pinpoint Dyna Striker's
location, so let's take it back.
What about Yomogi—?
No time to waste!
We're raiding the enemy base!
It's too dangerous for you.
Eh?!
Minami!
Did you ever watch the private video?
I did.
Yeah? And?
I don't know.
You couldn't tell if it was bullying?
Was it a gray area?
I'm telling you, I don't know.
Maybe I could take a look.
This has nothing to do with you.
Huh?
We should use it to negotiate.
Are you stupid?!
It'd be way more fun
wrecking shit in that thing!
This isn't about fun.
I don't care, so just decide already.
At this rate, I should've left it.
There it is.
Mujina stole it after all.
Koyomi, create an opening.
Huh? How?
Do something crazy.
Huh? Like what?
Figure it out yourself.
This is your fault.
Right...
In that case, we're the same.
Argh, jeez!
Koyomi?!
Get off me!
Nice one! Got it!
Access Mode... Dyna Striker!
I said, get off!
Why are you here?!
Sorry.
Bring it on, Kaiju Eugenicists!
Hey! This ain't good!
Indeed.
It's time to settle our 5,000-year grudge!
Wha—?! Damn!
They got away?! Shit! Lucky bastards!
That was a close one.
I thought I was dead.
There's always next time.
Prank... succe—
What's wrong?
Something happen?
It's nothing.
I see. Then I won't pry.
It's just...
Hmm?
I wish life was easier.
Even strong people
like you think that, huh?
I'm far from strong.
I think you're fine just as you are.
If only it was that simple.
It is. It really is simple.
Sorry, I have to go.
Mmm.
Minami?
What?
Was Sizumu here just now?
He was.
Did he—?
It was nothing.
Something happen?
Huh?
Another kaiju?
What's with this one?! I can't get it!
Mujina, help Onija out.
Huh? Me?
Kaiju must change for the world to change.
We must change, too.
Is that what kaiju tell you?
Kaiju definitely have a need for us.
Of course, that includes Mujina, too.
Instance Domination!
Hmm? We got it!
We did!
It takes two to control it.
Do it. Change the world with kaiju.
I feel like I finally get it.
What's up with you guys?
Nothing.
Whatever. Let's go!
Access Mode... Dyna Soldier.
Dyna Wing.
Dyna Striker.
Dyna Diver!
Here they come!
We're gonna crush 'em!
Combine Dragon Dynazenon!
Battle, Go!
Take this!
Ow!
Dynazenon! Is that all
the four of you got?!
Did your personality change?
Why's this thing so strong?!
No...
It's our power that's lacking!
Get a grip, people! We'll be crushed!
You don't think I know?!
Dyna Saber!
Now!
Super Dragon Dyna Rex!
It dodged!
Well, how about this?!
Yeah, take that! Crush 'em, Mujina!
That was my plan!
Gauma, I wish we could've talked more
before it came to this.
What the—?!
A giant?!
You were looking a little downcast and I wanted to have a chat
So I tried walking a whole step closer alongside you
The shadows were growing like a sundial's needle at sunset
You were striding so fast I thought the season'd change
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Just like your smiling face