It doesn't even look close!
Pay Stub
Yomogi Asanaka
25 May 2020
Whew, that's a lot.
Hey, Freshman. You pick up more shifts?
Helping the family out?
Oh, it's nothing like that.
Just wanted some spending money.
Aha.
Well, I'll get going.
We've gotta decide our project?
It's only May.
When's the festival?
Second week of October.
That's way off.
Ain't it?
How about a haunted house?
I heard they were banned.
Why?
Ghosts might show up.
Serious?
What?
Gimme a break.
No, I'm serious. Years back,
some teased student offed themselves.
If we cooked food, what should we do?
Huh? Who teases in high school?
Meat skewers.
Fried food? In class?
I know, right?
Why not?!
Now,
go and soar.
Whoa. That's dangerous.
It's Minami.
What's she doing up there?
Speaking of her...
I heard it, too.
What?
I guess she's asked a bunch of guys out.
Huh? She's that kinda girl?
She asks 'em out and ditches 'em.
Like some sort of promise-breaking affliction.
The hell's that?
It's just a rumor.
I can't picture her like that.
You're so pure, Yomogi.
What's that mean?
What's a Kaiju User?
— Episode 1 —
Fujiyokidai High School
Id ex id officia nemo pariatur. Molestias debitis officia a perferendis et. Voluptas atque eius blanditiis excepturi quas beatae. Soluta distinctio ex repellat ab enim at reprehenderit. Ea consequatur sequi dolorem ipsum consequuntur dolorum cumque. Sit quis ipsam corporis fuga ea aspernatur
I heard all about it, Yume.
About what?
You asked a 2nd-year
to meet you and ditched him.
Yeah. He went off on me yesterday.
You know, that kinda stuff gets around.
Yeah.
I hate to say it, but don't you know
your class talks about you?
Since you're not in my class,
why even care?
I've known you forever,
so I'm saying it for your own good.
Why, thanks, Mom.
Cut it out.
Yume. Stop making promises you won't keep.
Hello?
Don't ignore me.
About the different lines of thinking...
There's Stoic Asceticism
and Epicurus' Hedonism.
These two are like night and day.
In this class—
Year-over-year, more tombs
are being dismantled.
Hmm? Senpai, the memorial is next week.
Huh?
Ugh, you're right.
Good luck explaining you're unemployed.
Says the one who skips school.
That's different! I don't attend
school purely by choice.
This may very well be the new "grave."
That's different?
Bye, bye.
Bye.
Later.
Um, are you okay?
Starving...
Starving? R-Right. Um...
H-Here. It's leftovers from lunch,
but if you want it...
Whoa!
Well, I'll be going now.
You... saved my life.
Huh?
No, for real.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
What's your name?
Huh?
Your name!
My name? I-It's Yomogi Asanaka.
Yomogi, huh?
That's a good name.
Thank you.
I'm Gauma, a kaiju user.
Kaiju? Okay...
As for why I'm here...
Can you just let me go?
Thanks. I swear I'll return the favor.
Uh, it's actually fine if you don't, so...!
Yomogi!
Yomogi, let's go!
Okay!
We'll be back later, Mom.
Hmm?
We're having dinner with Kamijo.
Mmm.
Yomogi, let's go!
You're so loud.
Say something?
So loud.
And it's so good for the earth!
Yomogi, you're now in...?
High school.
Yeah, thought so. Which is why...
Here. Congrats.
Entering
School
Gift
What? My goodness!
Huh? Um...
Because you'll be
going out more, you know?
You shouldn't have, but thanks.
Thank you.
...and it talks automatically.
What are you doing, Yomogi? Let's go!
Donation
Box
It's another day in the life
of this big family!
The Hinode's morning starts...
Thanks for the meal.
Oh. Can I go in Kano's room?
I wanna borrow something.
What?
A book for school.
Sure, as long as you return it.
Yeah.
It's not like she's going to need it.
Honey!
Huh?
Clean up after yourself
before you start drinking.
There it is.
Respect for the Aged Day
Recital
Yume.
Respect for the Aged Day
Recital
Yume, I'd like you to come.
Why?
Clean up, huh?
It's about time you cleaned up, too.
Cleaned what?
Kano's room. Enough is enough.
What do you want from me?
6 pm
Eyewitness recordings
Tokyo - Imose
__________________
“As I was about to drive off from the parking lot,
the car suddenly started levitating.”
Vehicle Owner
Cars and other things levitate in the air
“Strange phenomena”
keep occurring
According to the police,
at around 6 o'clock...
Whoa. Check this out, Senpai.
Garbage was floating...
Hey, Senpai! Senpai!
Hey, hey, hey! Senpai!
And he grabbed me by the leg.
Whoa. Freaky.
Almost thought he'd eat me.
Hey! Yomogi!
Hey!
Shoot! I'm going ahead!
Huh? Who's that?
Hey, hey! Yomogi! It's me!
Looks like he's having fun.
Um...
Yeah?
Do you have time after school?
Huh? Today?
Yes.
Uh, um...
My name's Minami. Yume Minami.
Yeah, I know. You're in my class.
Oh, yeah.
I've gotta go to work tonight.
I see.
Oh, but I'll be done at eight.
Then, can you meet me here at nine?
Sure, but why?
Um... I thought if anyone,
maybe you would hear me out.
You saw me here, right?
Uh, yeah.
Heard the rumors about me?
Huh? No.
You don't have to pretend.
You don't believe me, though?
No, that's not true.
Good. I'll see you here. It's a promise.
Yeah.
Hey!
Yomogi!
Why do you keep running from me?!
What?
See you at nine! Bye!
Wait up, Yomogi!
You a friend of Yomogi's?
Hey, Freshman. Dinner later?
Today?
It's my treat.
Oh, sorry. I've got plans.
Ooh! So naughty!
What is? What?!
Hey, Senpai! It's nearby,
so let's go check it out!
What?
The floating car or building or whatever.
Ugh.
C'mon, let's go see it!
The police get nosy
when I walk around with you.
Whatever! Let's go outside!
Ugh.
Why does no one believe we're cousins?
Acheron Flood Gate
Lorem Ip
sum Dolor
Sit Amet
Wednesday, May 27
She didn't come.
I thought if anyone,
maybe you would hear me out.
For real?
We meet again, Yomogi.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing?
Can you just drop it?
Acheron Flood Gate
Lorem Ip
sum Dolor
Sit Amet
It's raining. You'll catch a cold.
You waiting for someone?
Oh, her! The girl from this morning?!
Nope.
I knew it! She your girlfriend?
No way.
What time you supposed to meet?
What time?!
Nine.
Whoa! She's 40 minutes late!
You not gonna search for her?!
Search?!
Fine, I'll go search for her!
'Cuz I owe you one!
Acheron Flood Gate
Lorem Ip
sum Dolor
Sit Amet
There you are!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, you!
Who are you?
You saw me before!
I'm Gauma, a kaiju user.
What's your name?
You made a promise with Yomogi.
Why are you here?
You're way late.
H-Hey! Where are you going?!
Wait up!
It's none of your business.
It is!
You...
You tricked Yomogi?
You weren't gonna go,
but you made him wait?
You toying with him?
And what if I was?
Acheron Flood Gate
Lorem Ip
sum Dolor
Sit Amet
Then we've got a huge damn problem!
Yomogi's been waiting in the rain!
The dude might even catch a cold!
Shut up.
You shut up!
Listen here!
Too close!
In this world, there're three things
important for people to keep:
Promises... Uh,
and you know... Love, and...
Can I leave?
I ain't finished yet!
Minami?
Yomogi...
Yomogi! You're being tricked!
Huh?
By her! She wasn't gonna
keep her promise from the start!
What? Meaning...?
She's toying with you and tricked you!
...like some sort of
promise-breaking affliction.
Is it true?
It's true.
Seriously?! I can't believe you!
Something wrong with you?
Something is wrong with me.
What?
Hey, hey, hey! It's here! It's a big one!
No use. I can't control the kaiju.
Kaiju?
It's glowing! It's ringing!
See?! Look! Something's moving!
Where?
Argh! I can't get a good photo!
If I lost my power as a kaiju user...
Hey! Be careful!
...then I'll just have to use this!
Whoa! This one's up close!
It's super pretty!
Shoot! It looked at me!
Where are its eyes?
It's coming this way!
Run!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
H-Huh?! Senpai!
Is he... dead?
Unemployed and dead.
Ouch!
Um, what is this? Huh?!
Minami? Where are we?
Yomogi?
I guess you need
four people to make it move.
Four? Huh? When did he get here?
Make what move?
Dy... na... zenon.
Was it you who took us in?
Is that your name?
That's a good name!
Dynazenon?
Let's go!
Huh? Where?
Um! Holy shit! Holy shit! Holy shit!
Senpai!
Found it!
It really is a kaiju!
This kaiju...! Is it them?!
In that case, let's do this
before it runs wild!
Dynazenon! Battle, Go!
Yeah
Huh? Should I be doing something?
Quit touching stuff!
S-Sorry!
I'll try my luck!
Just put your trust in me it's gonna work out alright
Huh? Try?
Yeah! This is my first time!
I can convince you even if it's gonna take all night
Whoa!
Cause there's something in my mind
Are you alive? Senpai, hello? Are you alive?!
I can picture inside me
Chise? I dunno what's going on.
It took away my breath
And my heart is breathing faster
It's chemistry at work
whenever we're together
A sign
Something tells me that you're gonna fall
What the hell? Wh-Whoa!
For my charms and my affection
Move in my direction
Shit! Is this the kaiju's power?!
Let me show I'm never wrong
I can tell this situation
The one that we've been waiting
All this time, I know!
Ow, ow! Shit!
Huh? Did we make it angry?
How can you tell, Yomogi?
Just look at it!
Huh? You guys know each other?
Wait, who are you anyway?!
Dynazenon... What exactly are you?
Before we're beat,
show us what you're made of!
Stand proud!
It all depends on us! We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness and all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
Th-That stopped it!
Is this Dynazenon's true power?! Dyna Rex!
If you look at the azure sky
You may find your heart torn
As you realise your own insignificance
The emotions dispersed throughout the city
Incommodius and unstable as they are
Are almost like an impuissant SOS
If you try and take someone's hand
You can find the root of their anxiety
I want to know why I met you solus
I want to know the reason for your solitude
Stand proud!
It all depends on us! We can nullify the melancholy of this world!
Eat this!
Blazing Inferno Rex Roar!
I want to take on all your overflowing sadness and all your weakness
I'll take it hand in hand
Alright it's go time
We're fighting to secure our futures
And you're really needed right now
You're needed
Hello, Senpai?! You alive?!
I dunno, but I think it's over.
What... just happened?
Minami, you okay?!
Something is wrong with me.
You were looking a little downcast and I wanted to have a chat
So I tried walking a whole step closer alongside you
The shadows were growing like a sundial's needle at sunset
You were striding so fast I thought the season'd change
I'd never put into words the real important stuff like love
Blink and you'll miss it, but that's what I put my faith in
Words of promise, my favourite flower, the treasure in my pocket
It seemed like you'd be torn away along with all those wonderful things
So I started running, not knowing if I'd make it, your hand in mine
This world probably isn't that vast
So I took another step forward today
It was ever so radiant
Just like your smiling face