Not many kaiju lately.
Maybe there're kaiju seasons.
—Hot seasons, dry seasons,
harvest seasons...
—Captain? What are you looking at?
—Hot seasons, dry seasons,
harvest seasons...
Huh? Look.
Huh? Hmm? What?
Up!
Up? O-Oh!
"Episode 10: Which Memories
Do You Regret?"
Up? O-Oh!
"Episode 10: Which Memories
Do You Regret?"
A kite!
"Episode 10: Which Memories
Do You Regret?"
"24-Hour Yomotsu Food Service"
First kaiju in a while.
This one looks different.
It's good. I was waiting
for one like this.
Can I go for it?
Of course.
Instance Dominat—
Huh? What the hell happened?
Mujina, what'd you do?!
She's gone.
Huh?
She just vanished.
Mujina! Where are—?!
Now everyone can be free.
Who's flying it?
The family over there.
It's so high.
It takes a good grip.
Yeah?
—I just made that up.
—Huh? What?
—Well, it might.
—Huh?
Oh, it flew away.
Gauma! Have you seen Minami?!
Huh? She's right there... or was.
Uh, I thought you were with her.
Papa... Mama...
Is this a dream? What's going on?
Kano's alive?
Hey, what the hell?!
People are vanishing.
Huh? Over there!
Shit! I knew it was a kaiju!
So that's what took Minami?
Thank you.
You're welcome. Was it good?
It was.
That's good to hear!
It makes cooking worthwhile.
Have I gone into the past?
Kano, the dishes! And your bento box!
Hey, Kano!
What was I thinking back then?
Not good. Let's clean this kaiju up.
But without Minami, we can't combine.
This might be tough.
Leave it to me.
Yeah, whatever. Just be grateful
we're letting you—
Sorry!
Knight, be careful.
I know. You be careful, too.
Knight!
This is...
I know where Dyna Wing's at—
inside the kaiju.
And Minami, too.
Let's get her back!
How?
By going through its mouth.
I'll go in first. You guys wait until I—
Hmm?
Gauma!
Well, I guess it's up to me.
The others!
Chise, we've gotta go!
But—!
I found it here. We could do
anything with this much.
Koyomi, let's use it and go somewhere.
That's right... This is when I ran away.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Where am I?
Gauma!
Wh-Why are you guys here?!
Dude, my clothes!
Excited much?
She's on her way.
Huh? Who?
The princess is coming
to observe our work.
Gauma, don't embarrass us.
I see... Oh, yeah...
I wonder why she cares about kaiju users?
Beats me.
Look.
The princess has arrived.
Princess!
Ow, ow, ow!
Is this inside the kaiju?
Gauma?! Huh?! What?!
Yomogi, there's someone
I want you to meet.
Who?
It's a friend of mine named Kamijo.
—I was hoping you'd join us for dinner.
—Why didn't I just say no?
Dyna Soldier...
Oh, yeah. I'm looking for Minami!
Dyna Soldier, show me the way!
Minami!
Minami! What the hell is all this?
Why is it broken?
Oh...
Futaba and Kano?
Is this Minami's past?
Goldburn. You protected us, didn't you?
Will Senpai and the others come back?
I think it all depends on them.
Kano?
Dammit!
What should I do, Dyna Soldier?
Kano, is chorus club fun?
Maybe I'll try it in high school.
Suit yourself.
You always say that.
Hmm?
Huh? What?!
Minami... Try to remember!
Yume.
Yume, I'd like you to come.
Huh?
To the chorus club's recital.
"33rd Fujiyokidai High School
Seasonal Recital"
"Wind Instrument" "Chorus Club"
"33rd Fujiyokidai High School
Seasonal Recital"
"Wind Instrument" "Chorus Club"
Okay.
It's a promise, then.
Yeah.
What?
Never mind.
I'm going out.
Singing practice?
Yeah.
Don't go somewhere dangerous.
Like on the flood gate?
Hey, don't you dare!
Kano!
They say it was suicide.
She died at that flood gate.
Minami, we've gotta
stop your sister! Otherwise...
Why can't I reach you?! At this rate—!
At this rate, Minami will be sad! And I...
I... can't stand that!
Dyna Wing?
Yomogi!
Minami...
Let's go stop your sister!
Right!
♬ Now, ♬
♬ go and soar. ♬
♬ On the winds ♬
♬ called hope. ♬
Kano! Kano! Kano!
Kano!
—Please don't die!
—Huh?
I know everything!
I know you're dating Futaba
and that you're being bullied!
And... and... this!
Hold up. Why would I die?
Huh?
I don't plan on dying.
Didn't I make you promise
to come to my recital?
Right, Yume?
Kano...
...it was an accident.
Kano wasn't like that.
Why do you look so big?
You never meant to break our promise.
This... It's awful!
It makes no difference
whether it's suicide or an accident.
I just... don't want Kano to die!
Die? So that's why you came and found me.
I should've got along with you better.
Sorry, Yomogi. Can you give me more time?
Got it. I'm going ahead.
Okay.
We'll all be waiting for you.
Everyone who vanished is stuck in the past
and it's up to me to bring them back!
Money to last a lifetime...
A lifetime of—
Koyomi!
Huh? Supervisor?
Hurry! Help me pick it up!
Who cares? It's probably not real.
And what if it is?! Argh, shit! Dammit!
Yomogi.
Let's go home, Koyomi.
—I...
—Koyomi.
Bastard! I'll kill you!
Why... did you... betray us?
You Eugenicists are the ones
who betrayed the country.
The country... wanted to
get rid of... us kaiju users.
They were just... using us.
Why do you care...
about a country... like that?
It's not the country I care about.
Prin... cess.
That person... taught me...
Promises, love, and...
Gauma! This is no time to die!
The Eugenicists revive in 5,000 years
and are trying to erase our world!
Our present time is getting wiped out!
Yomogi, you're my lifesaver after all.
Let's go back to our "now."
Knight, let's go back to our world!
I didn't need help.
It's embarrassing at home,
so I sang here a lot.
I never knew.
Yume, didn't you hate me?
That's not true!
You're always so agreeable.
Yume, you know what people want to hear.
That's not... true.
I was always envious of that.
I wished I was more like you.
That's why I pushed you away.
Huh?
In high school, I decided to
join the club and try to change.
I might've been spinning my wheels,
but Futaba was real nice to me.
Then you should've relied on him more.
Yeah, but I didn't want to be a bother.
Maybe I tried too hard.
So, please don't blame him.
Okay.
Make sure you rely on people.
Lately, I'm getting much better at it.
I see.
I kinda envy you after all.
Should I really go back to my own time?
Suit yourself, right?
You always say that.
Hey, look!
Thanks, Sis.
Sorry I'm late!
Welcome back, Minami.
Hi.
You back, Yume?
That kaiju took us into our pasts.
So let's give it a big thank you!
Dynazenon! Battle...
...Go!
Knight!
Right!
We have to hurry!
The whole world will disappear!
But what about the people
trapped in the kaiju?!
If you beat the kaiju and disable
its power, all the people should return!
—Then let's beat the kaiju...
...and get back our "now"!
All together!
Right!
Super Dragon King Kaiser Gridknight!
Now!
Powering up Dyna Saber!
Here it goes!
Kaiser Knight Circular!
You worried me sick, Senpai. You okay?
—I guess.
—So, you were betrayed
by the country you served?
—Now I'm hungry from worrying so much.
—So, you were betrayed
by the country you served?
—Now I'm hungry from worrying so much.
—I can't remember every damn thing.
—Me, too.
—Right? Let's grab something to eat!
—But... I thought I'd
get to meet her again.
—Like takoyaki, maybe?
—But... I thought I'd
get to meet her again.
—Like takoyaki, maybe?
—Huh?
I'm starving!
—Hmm?!
—Us, too.
Wanna go eat?
Absolutely!
Huh? Where's Minami?
♬ The blue skies that cover... ♬
Captain!
—Shoot, I collapsed from hunger.
—♬ Now, ♬
—Again?!
—Again?
—♬ Now, ♬
—Didn't I mention it?
—♬ go and soar! ♬
—The first time we met,
Gauma fell over from hunger.
Really?
—Just leave him behind.
—♬ On the winds called hope. ♬
—We should.