Gimme a sec.
Come on, do it!
Hurry up!
I can't do it!
Ugh, it's creepy.
Let's see.
What is it?
A kaiju?
A failed kaiju.
What the—?!
Damn cat.
What a gross face!
Man, talk about rude.
Is my face really that ugly?
Hey!
What Is This Wavering Emotion?
— Episode 8 —
The hell is this?!
What's up?
I guess they came to talk with Futaba.
Futaba?
That's right. He quit
a while back, though.
Um, do you have his contact info?
Of course we do,
but that's private information.
Oh, yeah.
Inamoto, what is this?
I found it here. We could
do anything with this much.
It's real?
Let's go somewhere together.
Somewhere?
I wonder why I got married?
It helped us realize
we should value each other more.
Chise
Calling
Message
Chise
Calling
Message
Chise
Calling
Message
Chise
Calling
Message
Hello?
Senpai? Where are you?
Gauma called an emergency meeting.
Be right there.
I'm sure Futaba will call eventually.
I hope so.
You wanna go somewhere?
Where?
Uh, well... Anywhere is fine.
Um...
What's this face?
Another kaiju?
Yeah. A kaiju got me.
Only a kaiju could do this!
Everyone, let's split up and find it!
Find it?
It's using power but hasn't shown itself.
True.
It could be a little kaiju.
I guess there's all types of kaiju.
It still might be nearby.
If we all look, we'll find it quick.
Don't let your guard down
or you'll become like me.
That would suck.
Is Gauma seriously saying there's
a kaiju that goes around coloring stuff?
There's one.
Huh?
There is one!
It's really small.
It's running!
Tell Gauma! I'll catch it!
Right!
No matter how small it is,
it's still a kaiju.
Huh?
What's his deal?
Catch it?
It fell on its own.
Look how cute it— Never mind.
Animal abuse is
punishable by law
Good job, Yomogi! Now I'll defeat it!
Defeat it? You're gonna kill it?
Don't we always?
Yeah, I guess so.
All right... Here goes.
W-Wait!
What now?!
Don't kaiju wreck things
'cuz the Eugenicists control them?
Yeah.
But you'll kill it when they're not?
Mmm?
Yeah, it's not hurting anything.
It's just coloring stuff.
Don't you think killing it sounds cruel?
Good point. Maybe you're right.
In that case, I'll control it
as a kaiju user.
Oh, yeah. Gauma's a kaiju user.
I've never seen him do it though.
Well, watch closely!
Instance Domination!
Are you controlling it right now?
It's no use. My power must've weakened.
Instance Domination!
Huh?
You making fun?!
Nah, but I thought I'd give it a shot!
That's not how kaiju users work!
You've gotta train and train your ass off.
Instance Domination.
You didn't train shit!
Go on. Let's see your training.
You are making fun.
I think I'll pass.
Instance Domination.
Huh?
Huh? Sweet!
Whoa!
Yomogi! Holy shit!
You did it.
You're kidding me!
You tricked us.
That was freaky.
What's wrong?
Nothing, but...
So, Captain? What to do with the kaiju?
Yeah, uh... I'll take it home
and keep an eye on it.
You'll keep it?
To see if it'll fix my face somehow.
But if it causes any damage, I'll kill it.
Until then, you'll look like that?
I might just kill it sooner.
Well, look who we have here!
You guys are still here?
Why should we have left?
Is that a kaiju I see?
It's rare for Sizumu
to invite us somewhere.
All we can do is wait for a kaiju,
so why not have fun?
Hey, hey, hey, hey! This looks fun!
Worried about kaiju being born
while we're in there?
Learn to loosen up!
Did you two always get along?
No way.
It's believed that kaiju have a source.
A source?
However, for kaiju to
appear this frequently,
their sources must be
purposely scattered around.
The Kaiju Eugenicists?
Mmm.
The human heart feeds the source.
Emotions give birth to and nurture kaiju.
How do you guys know that?
It's not like you're kaiju.
So a kaiju user like you
didn't know, Captain Gauma?
It's news to me. Kaiju users
don't need to know how kaiju are born.
This kaiju may be incomplete
because the human
responsible for it is, too.
Even so, it'll be dangerous if it grows.
You think?
I'm saying we can't leave it be.
That's why I'm watching it.
Won't it absorb emotions or something?
You mean, like mine?
Whatever. Just watch it closely.
I already said I would.
They grow through human emotions...
What?
Oh, nothing.
What?!
Wait, wait up! Hey!
Oh, shit! Stop pushing me, idiot!
Is it okay to be doing this?
At least you behave,
but you're really an eyesore.
That person was kind to living things...
Where are you, Princess?
In this world, there're three things
important for people to keep:
Promises, love, and...
It's already this late?
Sleepy!
Hey, hey, hey!
Before anyone asks,
I swear I was watching it!
But in an instant—
the instant I looked away...!
Gauma, that's three times.
Excuses aside, Captain,
what should we do now?
Let's split up and look for the kaiju!
It's Sunday, you know.
S-Sorry.
Whatever.
It's morning, Mujina.
Shall we head back?
Wanna see a movie?
Whoa, shouldn't we—?
Which movie?
You're going?!
Where is it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You serious?
FIRST GENERATION
FIRST
GENER
ATION
That sounds
awesome.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Knight?
That one kaiju got away.
I should've dealt with it back then.
I'll have to step in.
Huh? Do you have a way to find kaiju?
I do.
Seriously? What a relief!
Yomogi Asanaka, let's find the kaiju.
Uh, sure... and thanks. But, how?
Search till we find it.
Right.
Whoa, holy shit! This is sick!
Shut up!
You taking a break, too?
Yeah. No sign of the kaiju.
Tell me about it.
Watching a movie?
My battery's gonna die.
Do you think the kaiju has a heart?
Why do you ask?
Until now, I thought we had to kill kaiju
because they run amok.
But if it's like you're saying—
that kaiju are born from human emotions,
maybe there's kaiju with feelings like us.
Some kaiju do have hearts.
Then, what if this one—?
Others will fool you.
If you guess wrong
and people die, it's too late.
Why do you know so much about kaiju?
I just do.
If kaiju are a threat, I'll kill
without hesitation as I always do.
Hello?
Yomogi!
I found the kaiju!
Gauma!
Let's try to stop it together!
Right!
Access Mode... Dyna Diver!
Dyna Striker!
Since I messed up this time,
I've gotta defeat it!
It's dangerous to fire missiles here!
Good point.
I'll lure it outside the city
and you can hit it!
It feels like you're growing up, kid.
Hold up.
What?
I'm probably older than you.
But I'm plus five thousand.
Five thousand years.
Sh-Shut up.
What's up?
It's Sunday, so maybe it's an event.
I see.
A kaiju?
Hey! This way, this way!
This way, this way!
Nice, it's working!
Argh! The exit's gonna be packed!
Huh? Minami?
Chise!
Minami!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
If it's that big, it's dangerous. Kill it.
I guess the Eugenicists must've found it.
Koyomi!
It's doing damage. No time to hesitate.
Yomogi Asanaka,
let's defeat the kaiju together.
Together?
Let me use you.
Access Mode... Dyna Soldier!
What's this?!
It must have adapted to my presence.
Adapted?
Meaning, this!
Dynamic Cannon!
You're kidding!
Take aim, Yomogi Asanaka.
Should we really be killing it like this?
What if kaiju have hearts and emotions?
Yomo!
Bad news! Minami's still in there!
She is?!
We got split up while leaving!
Yomogi!
Minami?!
I'm still inside the building,
but my Dyna Wing—!
Minami! Minami!
Son of a—!
What are you doing?
There's no time to hesitate.
Please, work!
Instance Domina—!
Now! Do it, Yomogi Asanaka!
Dynamic Fire!
Yomogi...
Over here, Minami!
Sorry. I dropped Dyna Wing.
Least it wasn't stolen.
True.
She's not you.
Sorry. It's my fault this happened.
No, it's because I said something weird.
Yomogi...
When I was about to shoot, the kaiju...
It looked at me.
Hope it was just my imagination.
Kaiju are kaiju.
Huh?
That was amazing!
FIRST GENERATION
FIRST
GENER
ATION
Yeah, I thought I was dead!
When the water spewed up
like that, it was incred—
Are you feeling down?
No, not really.
What?
Thanks.
Huh?
I heard you saved everyone from the kaiju.
It was Knight more so than me, but...
Are you hungry?
Starving.
Wanna go somewhere?
Where?
Anywhere is fine.
Mmm.